AIRPLANE ENGINE HUMS
Music: "Semi-Charmed Life"
by Third Eye Blind
# Do do do, do do-do do
# Do do do...
HORN HONKS
GIRL: Awesome.
# I'm packed, and I'm holding,
I'm smiling, she living
# She golden,
she lives for me
# Says she lives for me...
Hey, does Mom know
you drive like that?
Whatever, OK?
Can you get your stuff?
I'm missing 90210.
You're lucky you have
all that gear in your mouth,
cos they'll need your teeth to
identify your charred remains.
Shut up! You're such a dick!
Bye, Nicole.
MAN: ...time apart. That's all.
WOMAN: Where is this coming from?
You can come, all right?
It's not...
Never mind. You don't want me
to come, I'm not coming.
Fine.
Then I want you out. Bye!
Am I a partner, or am I not?
You don't support me and my band.
I support the band.
I love the band.
Just get in the car.
Don't hurry back.
Come on!
You missed a spot right here.
# ..do do-do do
# Do do do, do do-do do
# I want something else...
Can I clear these for you, sir?
Will you be wanting
any more peanuts?
I think they have another crate
in the galley.
Thanks.
Oh, dear. All right, then.
I'll just be getting you a towel.
Oh, dear, I'm...
oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
KNOCK ON DOOR
I'm fine, thank you.
KNOCKING
There's towels in here,
so I don't really need...
# Do do do, do do-do do
# I want something else. #
Everything all right, sir?
Every...yeah.
Everything's good. Thanks.
PA: Your attention, please.
There has been a luggage carousel
change for flight 640.
It will now be on carousel 4.
Don't.
I'm Oliver.
I just thought
we'd chat it up...
Blah, blah, blah.
See, it's ruined.
What's ruined?
Our little secret.
Actually, I think the stewardess
was kind of onto us, so...
Well, she'll have to be killed.
I'm Oliver.
You keep saying that.
Wow. You don't make it
easy for a guy.
I think I made it pretty easy
for ya, Oliver.
So, what's Bon Jovi do?
Who?
Boyfriend.
Ex-boyfriend.
Yeah, I noticed that.
So, what happened there?
What, are we friends now?
I'd say we're a little bit more
than friends.
Bon Jovi get a big record contract
or somethin'?
His name's not Bon Jovi.
Oh.
He plays guitar.
Everyone plays guitar.
You play guitar?
No.
Strike two.
Strike two?
What was strike one?
Would you like to sit
next to your girlfriend?
Thank you very much.
I'd love to.
"So, what's your deal, Oliver?
You in New York on business?"
"Me? Oh, uh...
well, thank you for asking.
"No, actually I'm here
visiting my brother.
"He's a lawyer... Well, he's going
to be. He's in law school, so..."
Is that what you wanna do, too?
I don't know.
I just finished school.
Don't people usually
graduate in June?
Yeah.
It's almost a year ago.
You still don't have a job?
Who are you, my mom?
I don't know. When you look at me,
do you see your mom?
What sign are you?
What sign am I?
Cancer.
Strike three.
Thanks.
It's Emily.
I'd have never guessed Emily.
Don't get mugged.
Nice to meet you too, Oliver. I'm
Carol. I've heard a lot about you.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were...
Yeah.
MUSIC: "Walkin' On The Sun"
by Smash Mouth
IMITATES ELVIS PRESLEY:
Thank you very much.
# It ain't no joke
I'd like to buy the world a toke
# And teach the world to sing
in perfect harmony
# And teach the world to snub the...
Where'd it go?
What?
My jacket.
It was right there.
What jacket?
# This is a love attack
# I know it went out, but it's back
# It's just like any fad...
I ain't seen no jacket.
What?
What can I get for 20?
20?
Dollars?
# So don't delay, act now,
supplies are running out
# Allow, if you're still alive,
six to eight years to arrive
# And if you follow
there may be a tomorrow
# But if the offer's shunned
# You might as well
be walkin' on the sun
# You might as well be
walkin' on the sun
# You might as well
be walkin' on the sun. #
You know, kissing a smoker
is like licking an ashtray.
Really?
What's screwing one like?
You stalking me?
Yes.
Oh, somebody
stole my jacket.
What are you doing?
You wanna do something?
What,
are we friends now?
Ah, here she is.
I thought you were using
the ladies'.
I was. But, um...
SHE COUGHS
I just came out to get some air.
Hi, I'm Brent,
Emily's father.
Hi. Oliver.
Christine.
My stepmother.
So, you ready
for some Guggenheim?
You know what?
Can I...would you mind
if I skipped the museum?
Oh, Em,
Christine took off work.
I know. I'm sorry.
It's just, um...
Would you mind
if I tell them?
No, not at all.
Go ahead.
Oliver is getting some test results
back today,
and he was just wondering
if I could go with him.
It's a scary time.
It's OK.
So it won't take long.
Oh, don't you worry
about that.
You take as long as you need.
I'm sure everything
will turn out fine.
You'll see.
Good luck.
I'll see ya later?
OK.
Thanks.
You know, stuff like that's
not even funny.
You only get one chance
to make a first impression.
What do you care
what my dad thinks?
What if we hit it off,
become a thing or something?
What was that?
You and I would never
become a thing.
Oh! You really think pretty
highly of yourself, don't you?
First of all,
why would I get mixed up
with a guy
who I know first-hand
will jump into
an airplane bathroom
with the first girl
that comes a-knockin'?
That was with you.
You don't wanna
get mixed up with me
because I slept with you?
Second of all,
you're not even close
to being my type.
Well, I'm not lookin' for
a girlfriend anyway, so...
And thirdly,
it turns out
you might be gay.
I mean, I want a girlfriend.
Whatever.
Just first things first,
you know?
What things?
I don't know.
Just make a plan
and get all my ducks in line.
You mean ducks in a row?
Yes, I mean ducks in a row.
Well, what ducks are those?
Like the normal kind
of ducks...
Like job, career,
house, future.
And what,
then the girl of your dreams
will just come and find you?
Yep.
I'll find her.
We'll find each other.
Don't worry about me
and girls, OK?
I do all right.
Here.
MUSIC: "Save Tonight"
by Eagle-Eye Cherry
What's that?
Stop. Get outta here.
You're not unattractive.
# Go on and close...
You do realise it's the middle
of the afternoon, right?
Mm-hmm.
# You and me and a bottle of wine
# And hold you tonight
# Oh, yeah
Two more?
You know what? I still got stuff
to do today, so...
So do I.
You know what?
Make 'em doubles.
They are doubles.
# Let's delay our misery
# Save tonight
# And fight the break of dawn...
HE BURPS, THEN SIGHS
# Tomorrow I'll be gone...
26.
You know what?
I got it.
I know.
You know.
You know what?
I don't mind paying,
But I hate the fact that
you assume that I'm paying.
That's just...I mean,
at least make a move.
Like, make the reach
for it or something.
What if you don't get
your ducks in a row?
I'll get my ducks in a row.
In a line.
What if
it takes 20 years?
It's not gonna take 20 years.
It's gonna take five years.
Six, maybe. Max.
You don't even
have a job.
You don't even have
an inkling of a job.
See, that's not true.
I'm kinda interested
in all the stuff going on
with the internet.
Well, that's good.
I hear that's gonna be huge.
It will be.
I'm sure.
Are you being sarcastic?
No!
I think you're gonna be
beating away chicks with a stick.
Do you really think
that six years from now,
a guy like me,
with a job, a house,
a car...a nice car...
and a future,
you think I'm gonna have
a problem findin' somebody
to fall in love with me?
Oh, I think you're gonna
have a big problem.
You...
What are you doing?
I am writing down
my parents' phone number.
You live with your parents?
No.
Yes. But not
in six years, I won't.
What does six years have
anything to do with it?
Yeah, well, if you let me
finish, it's my whole...
it's my whole point.
Six years from now,
you call this phone number.
My parents
will answer the phone.
You ask 'em how to reach me.
They'll give you the number.
Then you call my house,
and when my beautiful wife
answers the phone,
Then you can ask her where to
send the 20 bucks you owe me.
20 bucks? I thought
you were gonna be some
hotshot businessguy.
Fine.
50. 50 big ones.
50 it is.
Whoa.
MUSIC: "Mint Car"
by The Cure
# The sun is up
I'm so happy I could scream
# And there's nowhere else
in the world I'd rather be...
Any time before Christmas.
# Than here with you,
it's perfect...
I'm saving my film.
For what?
For your trip?
This is your trip.
It's happening right now.
Don't...be careful. I got it
for Christmas, so don't...
Oh, no.
You're not shooting me.
SHUTTER CLICKS
Oh. All the places
I've travelled.
Nice. Mom's gonna
love that one.
Look alive.
Look, act really natural
in your surroundings.
Look sexy. Let's see
Ollie being sexy.
SHE LAUGHS
Ooh, I like it.
There you go. That's good.
Yeah!
Make love to the tree.
Now give it to me.
Give me the camera.
"Please."
Would you give me
the camera?
Are you done?
You're out of film.
No.
How did you shoot
a whole roll?
You're very shootable.
Did I not just say
I'm saving the film?
Hey.
Did you get the right film?
I don't know.
400 speed?
I just got film.
Was there change?
Shut up.
Give me that.
SHUTTER CLICKS
I gotta go.
OK.
So...
Don't.
You'll ruin it.
WOMAN GROANS PASSIONATELY
That was, uh...
That was pretty good.
Pretty good?
All right, awesome.
Mm-hmm.
Mind-blowing.
Out of this world?
Is that working for ya?
Yeah.
Yeah? All right.
Where are you going?
Em, I gotta work.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God, are you serious?
I thought I was terrible.
OK, wait, let me
just get a pen. Hold on.
Honey.
OK, go ahead.
Uh-huh.
Is that the Valley?
OK. No.
Am I gonna be late?
OK, OK. I will.
I will.
OK, thank you.
OK. Bye.
I got it. I got it!
You...what?
You got the part?
No, I got a callback.
But still!
It's one of those low-budget
independent films, but who cares?
Sweetie, will you just run
my lines with me before I go?
OK, what do you think?
I don't wanna look too desperate,
even though I am.
What are you doing?
I'm going.
Honey, you don't have to go.
You can have
two whole hours here.
No, Em.
I mean...
I'm going.
I'm sorry.
Martin, please,
listen to me.
LINE READER: Let go, Alexa.
It can't end this way,
Martin, not like this.
You should've thought
of that before, Alexa.
Don't turn your back
on me, Martin.
You owe me more than that.
I don't have any more
to give, Alexa.
You've taken it all.
I'm sorry, just...
Look at me, Martin...
DIRECTOR: OK, thank you.
Sorry. I just lost
my place. Sorry.
Emily, Emily, it's...
it's very, very good.
Just try and keep in mind
how much you love him.
Martin?
Yeah.
OK.
He's the love
of her life, OK?
So how would that make her feel
if he was leaving her?
Desperately unhappy?
Exactly.
Just one more thing. Try and keep
in mind she's a vampire.
OK, here we go.
And action.
You're better off.
That's what I think.
Of course
she's better off.
Dumps you right before New Year's.
It's awful.
I didn't want to say
anything to you while
you were seeing him...
Here, Dallas.
It's always gotta be
about him.
Well, I didn't see Peter
that way at all.
He could be too nice.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
But she's still better off.
Oh, she is much better off.
She's better off.
When it's over, it's over.
You're coming tomorrow,
aren't you, Em?
She's coming.
Hey, how about a blind date?
I know someone.
You can't take a blind date
to New Year's.
Why?
Why? Because it's
a blind date. You don't roll
the dice on New Year's.
Well, you don't go to New Year's
alone, either.
Why not? I'm going alone.
Well, that's you.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
I'm just sayin'.
The point is
is that it's New Year's,
and you know,
date or no date,
You just don't
spend New Year's alone.
Don't. She quit.
MUSIC: "There She Goes"
by the Getaway People
# All decked out
in her designer clothes
# Cos she's shootin' from
the hip with a credit card
# Everybody thinks
she's a bittle lit old
# But you can't take long
on an eyesore
# Drivin' in a Beamer
with the top down...
Hi. Um, is David there?
Hi. Is Chris there?
Hi. I was looking for Frank.
# A stick and stone
may break the bone
# But it don't quench the fire...
Yeah. No, most people... most
normal people have plans, you know,
Being that it's New Year's
and all, but thanks anyway.
Do you happen
to know if he...
if he'll be back later or...
Oh.
What's your name?
# Now stepping stones
and lickin' bones
# And cast them all aside
# I wonder what
she's looking for tonight
# And there she goes again
# There she goes again
TELEPHONE RINGS
RINGING
Hello. Martin residence.
Hello?
Hey...he-hello?
Hi.
Is Oliver there?
Yes, just a second.
Oliver!
Yeah?
Telephone!
OLIVER: Hello.
Hello.
Oliver?
This is.
This is Emily.
I don't know
if you remember me.
Wait. Emily, New York Emily?
Yeah.
GIRL: Hello?
I got it, Ellen.
Hello?
OK. God, I didn't know.
Sorry.
What a goofball, huh?
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
You still there?
Yeah, yeah. I'm here.
So what's up?
No, I was just...
I was just wondering...
I just came across your number
all of a sudden,
And I was just thinking to myself...
SHE CLEARS HER THROAT
You know, "Wow, I wonder
what Oliver's doing."
You know, I know that
you're probably busy tonight,
But I was just wondering
if you wanted to grab
a coffee this afternoon.
Sure.
So, really?
ELLEN: Oliver.
I'm on the phone, Ellen.
I know.
When you gettin' off?
I'm expecting a call.
You got a pager, Ellen.
But I can't talk on a pager.
Ellen, get off the phone!
You are such a dick!
Get off the phone, Ellen!
Mom, tell Ellen
to get off the phone.
Ellen!
Hello? Sorry about that.
CHUCKLES
You still there?
Yeah.
Uh, where are you?
I ll come over.
Now?
Yes. Why don't I...
why don't I come over?
DOORBELL BUZZES
SHE SPITS
Hello?
MAN: Hello. It's me.
Hey. The gate's broken,
so just give it a jiggle
and then just push.
BUZZING
Hi.
I'm Emily.
I'm Oliver.
You're not Oliver.
Ahh!
That's it? I thought you'd at least
invite him in.
You owe me 10.
I knew he wasn't you.
You're not that good-looking.
She didn't say that.
Wait, what did he say?
What did he tell you I said?
I said you were good-looking.
Told you.
That's what I said.
You...
He's a little...
He's saying you're crazy.
Yeah, I got that.
HORN HONKS
Did she honk?
Why?
My wife. I'm going.
Bye.
Bye. Bye.
Hi.
You look different.
So do you.
But, like, good different.
You, too. I like your hair.
Thank you.
I'm still signing.
Why? I don't know.
I'm stopping. OK.
Your brother screen
all your dates?
This is a date.
Can I get you anything to drink?
A tea or a soda?
I'm good, thanks.
Just go grab a beer.
I can't believe
you just assumed
That this was
what this was about.
You can't...
you can't believe I assumed
that what was about the what?
Because I'm not the same girl
you met three years ago.
I mean, I'm the same girl,
But it's not at all
the same situation.
Right. I understand.
I'm not one of those girls
who needs to sleep with someone
after every stupid breakup
Just to prove
she's still got it. I...
Yeah.
What are you doing?
I am looking
for your crazy pills.
You know, they have to be
around here somewhere
for moments like these, right?
That's not funny.
What if I really was crazy?
Have you eaten today?
How can you live in LA
And not have a car?
I had a car. Then I sold it.
I needed the capital
for my business.
That's right.
The plan. The ducks.
It's all coming back
to me now.
Only...two and a half more years
until you're rich.
Is your beautiful wife gonna live
in your parents' basement with you?
I don't live
with my parents.
Just visiting?
No, I was just pickin' some
stuff up, cos I'm moving.
"Diaperush.com"?
That's what it says.
We sell diapers on the internet.
I thought the whole internet thing
was done already.
No. Just need
a good business plan.
Diapers?
So, how's Bon Jovi?
Does he still rock?
Who?
Oh, him. He switched bands
and moved to Seattle.
Nice. Hope he knows
how to steam milk
and make those little
chocolate shavings.
Big talk coming
from a diaper salesman.
Oh, OK.
And the latest breakup?
What's he do?
Is he a baseball player
or a cosmonaut?
Who said I had a breakup?
You did,
in your kitchen during
your hypoglycemic rant.
So? Spill it.
Who's the guy?
I'm not telling you.
Did you dump him?
No. He dumped you.
I'm not gonna talk
about it.
OK. Fine. Then I'm
not talkin' at all.
You're not talking?
You ain't gettin' boo
outta me.
Fine, I'm not
talking, either.
SHE COUGHS
SHE CHOKES
Are you OK?
OK, fine. I'll tell you.
Mmm.
My brother's deaf, Em.
I can go days
without talking.
Can we get a check,
please?
I met him in class.
Yeah? You went back to school?
Acting class.
Oh, he's an actor.
Wow, actors.
That's like one rung up
from musicians.
He was a writer.
Is a writer.
Hmm. Hi. Could I
get a coffee?
Mm-hmm.
Just regular black.
After you.
Oh, sorry. Go ahead.
Frappuccino, please.
OK.
I believe the question
was who dumped whom?
He left me.
I got it.
No, I got it.
No, but I appreciate
the reach.
The acting classes are really
paying off, but I got it.
Shut up. I got it.
So what are your plans?
Plans for what?
Tonight.
It is New Year's.
Yeah. I'm not a really big
New Year's guy.
Bunch of amateurs
getting drunk.
Yeah.
Cringy people wearing
those party hats.
Ah! The hats.
Lame.
I know of a party.
Really?
Let's go.
You got more clothes
in your trunk
Than I got
in my whole closet.
Try this.
Nice.
Is this Bon Jovi's?
Am I supposed to act
Like I'm some big
Hollywood-producer type
or something?
Just be yourself.
Except maybe don't mention
the whole diaper thing.
Hey, Emily,
I gotta ask you somethin'.
Hey, do you mind?
Sorry.
What? What do you
have to ask me?
Well, what
was strike one?
What?
In New York.
Strike two was that I
didn't play guitar.
Strike three was that
I was born under
the wrong star sign.
What was strike one?
Strike one was that
I had to make the first move.
I got strike one
before we even met?
You can't get strike one
before you step up
to the plate.
You drive.
MUSIC PLAYS
I introduced myself.
What?
In New York.
I introduced myself.
That's not a move?
Who called who today?
I didn't have your number.
You never asked.
SHE GASPS
You came!
And with a young man
in tow.
This is Michelle
and Michelle's fiance Michael.
Hi.
Oliver.
I sell diapers.
Well, it's nice to meet you.
Yeah.
Hello, ladies.
Oh, my God!
Look at you.
Get you a drink?
I'm good, thanks.
I think I'll get one.
Uh-uh. You are not
getting off that easy.
He's an old friend.
I wish I had
an old friend
that looked like that.
He's gorgeous.
Come on, give it up.
Uh-oh.
Very carefully,
I want you to move backwards
in the direction of the bar.
TELEPHONE RINGS
Hello?
Ellen, it's me.
What do you want, Oliver?
Listen, I'm at this
big Hollywood party,
And I just ran into
that...the white rapper
guy you like.
Eminem? No way!
So listen.
So I'm sitting at the bar,
right, and we're talking,
and outta nowhere,
he starts running his hand
up and down my leg.
Happy New Year, Ellen.
You're such a dick, Oliver.
Thank you.
Eminem's here?
Who is he talking to, her?
Some guy.
Now he's talking to her.
She just kissed him.
Kissed who?
Peter. She's kissing Peter.
Is he kissing her back?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't hear you.
It sounded like you said
you sell diapers.
There you are!
Come on.
# Feel the vibe,
feel the terror, feel the pain
# It's drivin' me insane
# I can't fake,
for god's sakes
# Why am I drivin'
in the wrong lane?
# Trouble is my middle name,
but in the end, I'm not too bad
# Can someone tell me
if it's wrong to be so mad...
Put your hands on my ass.
That'll really get him.
# Mad about you
SHE GIGGLES
Do you want me to put my hands
on your ass?
You all right?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go...I'm gonna
go to the ladies' room.
I'll be right back.
MUSIC: "Bodyrock"
by Moby
EMCEE:
Come on in here, y'all,
cos this is New Year's,
and y'all know how this goes.
Here we go.
It's time for the countdown.
10, 9,
8, 7,
6, 5,
4, 3,
2, 1!
Happy New Year!
SHE LAUGHS
Clearly...
Clearly, you're not a fan of...
Shh!
You're cl...
I'm serious.
My neighbours are, like,
flip-out kind of people.
Ooh.
OK, that's enough.
Having a problem?
Very serious.
You OK?
I'm fine.
Oliver.
You've been robbed.
I'm moving.
You are?
Yeah. I told you.
You did?
Well, it's official.
The power's off.
When did you tell me?
Earlier.
My business,
it's in San Francisco.
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
Ollie.
Yeah?
SHUTTER CLICKS
Ah, nice. Thank you.
Hey, I took this.
Yeah, I know.
You framed it.
Yeah.
I liked it.
You framed my picture.
It's a good picture.
Wow.
Just when
I'm starting to like you,
you're moving away.
Can I tell you something?
Mm-hmm.
I think that...
That it's time that...
I think it's time
that I stop...
..being somebody's...
..girlfriend.
Hold on one second.
Just one sec.
Don't move.
Emily?
SHE SNORES
You OK?
SHE MUMBLES
You gonna throw up?
SHE SNORES
DOOR CLOSES
Hey, baby!
I'm home.
Sorry I'm late.
I got hung up at the office.
On the phone with some
bean counters from Huggies.
Did you remember
the wine?
The what?
The wine.
I forgot. You know what?
I'll get it right now.
Mm-mmm. Don't bother.
I already picked it up.
Why'd you ask me if I got it
in the first place?
Because I knew you wouldn't remember
that I asked you.
I knew you'd forget it.
Well, that's something
of a self-fulfilling
prophecy, then, huh?
Do you know what, Oliver?
You're never here.
And even when you are here,
you're still not here.
I'm here right now.
You seen my red shirt?
I can't do it anymore,
Ollie.
Can't do what?
This.
What are you trying to say?
I don't know, Ollie.
I just...
I think we need
to take a break.
DOORBELL RINGS
MUSIC: "Trouble"
by Ray LaMontagne
# Trouble
# Trouble, trouble, trouble, trouble
# Trouble been doggin' my soul...
Hi. Do you mind
if I just...
Oh, I'm sorry. I was...
I was gonna get that.
Well, there's a bunch more.
Right. You wanna trade?
No, thanks.
I'm gonna take this one.
Aha. So I see you knew
it was the import.
Very sneaky. Very sly.
It's got the acoustic b-side.
Yes, and a bonus track.
So you see my dilemma.
I can't possibly allow you
to walk out of this store
with the last copy.
I'm not just gonna walk out.
I'm gonna pay for it first.
Wait a minute.
Don't I know you?
Oh, jeez, spare me
the pickup line. Here.
No, it wasn't a pickup line.
I do know you.
Michelle's wedding.
Michelle Foster.
I went to school
with her husband.
Oh. Yeah, wait.
Ben something.
That's right. Ben Miller.
That's right. And you are...
CLICKS FINGERS
Uh, Emily.
Here.
No, I couldn't.
Come on. Just take it.
Really, it's yours.
No, just take it.
Seriously, I feel bad. Take it.
It's yours.
You know you want it.
I do want it.
Take it. Here.
Really?
Yeah.
Can't believe
you just took it.
Airport.
Yeah.
Dude. Dude,
this is what I want,
Exactly like this...
all black like Batman.
Very cool.
Yep.
What are you doin'?
Test-driving.
Hop in the back, dude.
Yo, you should get one, too,
like Batman and Robin.
Except without the tights.
It's like...
where you gonna park it?
This thing? Wherever I want.
I mean, this...
we're not in the money yet.
You heard your brother,
all right?
I mean, we wow 'em in New York,
it's a lock.
Come on. Hop in.
You know what?
I'm gonna stick around here
and finish some stuff up.
Would you relax, please?
Dude, take a step back, man.
You're startin to depress me.
Go take a weekend off. Do
somethin'for yourself, all right?
SHUTTER CLICKS
Beautiful.
Gorgeous.
Come on, Hailey.
Wait. Hailey!
Hailey, hold on.
Sweetie.
Oh, my God,
are you guys kidding?
Get a room.
Oh, I can't help it.
He's so hot.
Hi. Emily.
Oh, thank God
you can't get pregnant
when you're pregnant.
Hi.
So, you and Ben went
on a little date, huh?
Yeah. We had lunch.
It was nice.
And that's all I'm gonna
get outta you, isn't it?
Yeah.
Well, then I should probably
get back to work.
Bye, hon.
Bye, sexy.
Bye.
Lunch? What's the matter?
You don't like him?
Why do you say that?
Just cos we didn't jump
right into the sack?
What's jumpin' in the sack?
It's a game people play
at picnics, honey.
Hey.
I do weddings, head shots,
baby showers...
You know, for the money.
But I met a girl at a party...
she owns a gallery...
And she said she might
show my work there, so...
That's really cool.
How'd you do that?
You leave the shutter open.
The hard part's staying still.
Otherwise, you're just a blur
Like the cars in the background.
I'm gonna go splash
some water on my face,
so make yourself at home.
Wait, he just landed on your
doorstep? Honey, that's perfect.
Don't get excited.
He lives 400 miles away.
Emily, let's not get picky.
And I couldn't look
less sexy.
Oh, stop it.
You're gorgeous.
Has he put the moves on you yet?
He's not the type.
Someone's gonna have sex.
Shh. Will you stop it.
I gotta go. Wish me luck.
You don't need it.
Call me.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I mean, she owned
a business, right?
Like, selling antiques.
And she used to work
for the mayor's office
as an advisor,
But she said
she didn't like it, so...
wow, two careers already.
Yeah. So I thought
that she would understand,
you know, the kind of work
that you gotta put in
when you're first
startin' out, but...
she said that she couldn't be
number three or number four
on someone's list
of priorities.
She said
she could be number two,
But not if number one
was selling diapers.
TELEPHONE RINGS
MICHELLE: Hi.
It's me calling to see
how things are going.
This is...hi. Hello?
It's
a work-related call.
I'll just be one second.
Yes, can you get the...
please figure out
if the negatives
are gonna be ready
by tomorrow.
What?!
How's it going?
It's not.
It'll be fine,
As long as you're not wearing
that orange sweatshirt.
Don't call back here.
Sorry about that.
I just...
Where are you going?
What's your stance
on pancakes?
I'm pro pancakes.
Do you know
what you're gonna have yet?
I just can't...
I can't decide
what to get.
Come on, Ollie,
you gotta just let it go.
Smile.
You're here with me.
There it is.
That's the one.
Hi.
Oh, my God, Gina, hi!
How are you?
I'm good. How are you?
I'm good. It's been
such a long time.
Really long, yeah.
I've been meaning
to call you.
Me, too.
I was hoping that
we could actually get together
and talk a bit.
Yeah, that would be great.
It would be good.
Yeah.
Do you have
a couple of bucks
for the waitress?
Em. Hi.
Hey.
Uh, it's...
How's everything?
How are you?
I'm good.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You're good? Oh, great.
I was gonna sneak on by,
but then I thought,
"I saw you, so you probably saw me"
and...
Yeah, no, it's good
that you both said hi.
I knew
that she'd be fine with it.
I mean, it's been
a long time.
Yeah, no,
I m glad you sa...
Hi.
Hey.
Oliver.
Peter.
Oh, Oliver.
Good to see
you again.
Um, you know,
we should probably go
if we're gonna
catch that film.
Oh. You're right.
Em, take care.
Yeah, take care.
It was good to see you.
Bye.
Nice meeting you!
Oh, I'm starvin'.
Let's get outta here.
OK.
All right!
Come on. Let it go.
Smile. You're with me.
Shut up.
SHE HONKS HORN
Get off the road, grandma!
Come on.
Let it go.
Smile. You're with me.
No.
Hmm? Hmm?
Where we goin'?
We're headin' north.
I've been killin' myself
at work.
Nights, weekends.
Even at home.
Well, Bridget's home.
See, I moved in with her.
That was my big mistake
right there.
I shoulda stuck with the plan.
I mean, the plan was working.
You know, the irony of it
is that Bridget
actually loves plans.
We used to go on these trips.
She would plan everything
down to, like,
the very last detail.
I mean, like, including, like,
the gas station that we were
gonna stop at.
MUSIC ON RADIO:
"If You Leave Me Now"
by Chicago
I remember this one time.
We were in Ashland, right?
SHE SINGS: Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-oh,
baby, please don't go
We were at this
b&b station, right?
# If you leave me now...
And it starts raining, right?
And I'm not talkin'
about regular rain.
It was like
torrential-downpour rain.
# Ooh-ooh-ooh, no,
baby, please don t go...
So Bridget comes up
with this great idea, right?
# Just want you to stay
Park the car in the car wash,
because who's gonna wash
their car when it's raining?
# A love like ours
is love that's hard to find
# Find
BOTH: # How could we
let it slip away?
Come on.
# We've come too far
to leave it all behind
# How could we let it slip away?
# When tomorrow comes...
MUMBLES WORDS
# ..today...
THEY LAUGH
Do you want something?
Um, just...
just pick something.
SHE LAUGHS
Did you buy the whole store?
Aah!
Mmm.
Want some pie?
You want some Cheetos?
Oh, look at the moon.
Mm.
Let's pull over.
Did you love him? Peter?
No.
Maybe a little.
Do you love Bridget?
Yeah, I guess so.
Well, do you, or don't you?
I thought I did.
Well, if it wasn't love,
it was a lot like it.
OK, now I don't know.
Sounds stupid
when I say it out loud.
Honestly, if you're not
willing to sound stupid,
you don't deserve
to be in love.
Take this.
What?
What was that?
That.
I didn't hear
anything.
Aah!
Oh, my God! Oh!
Oh, my God. Are you OK?
Ollie, are you OK?
Aah!
Whoa, you just looked.
No, I didn't.
You said
you weren't gonna look.
I didn't look. Go.
I looked.
Ooh, looking good.
Shut up.
Ooh, very nice.
You're just taking advantage
of me right now. Come on.
OK, the shutter's
gonna stay open
for 40 seconds.
You have to keep
very still, OK?
OK.
Are you ready?
Ready.
CAMERA WHIRRS
Ooh! Ow! Ow!
Ooh, it's cold.
MUSIC: "Brighter Than Sunshine"
by Aqualung
# I never understood before
# I never knew what love was for
# My heart was broke,
my head was sore
# What a feeling...
Hi.
No moving.
# Tied up in ancient history
# I didn't believe in destiny
# I look up, you're standin'
next to me...
You're moving.
I can't help it.
# What a feelin' in my soul
# Love burns brighter
than sunshine
# Brighter than sunshine
# Let the rain fall, I don't care
# I'm yours, and suddenly you're mine
# Suddenly
# Suddenly you're mine
# And it's brighter than sunshine
# I never saw it happening
# I'd given up and given in
# I just couldn't
take the hurt again
# What a feelin'
# I didn't have the strength to fight
# But suddenly it all seemed so right
# Me and you
# What a feelin'
# What a feeling...
Folks, can I talk to you
out here for a second?
# Love burns brighter
than sunshine...
Folks.
# Let the rain fall, I don't care
# I'm yours, and suddenly you're mine
# Suddenly you're mine
# And it's brighter
than sunshine. #
Folks,
this is a national park.
Why don't you get
back in your clothes,
back in your car,
and back on the highway.
Have a nice day.
I gotta go.
OK.
So anyway,
we got this, uh,
big VC meeting in New York.
Gotta put on this big
dog and pony show.
You know what VC is, right?
No.
It's venture capital.
It's like a big influx of cash
to really help us
grow our business.
It sounds exciting.
I'll grab this.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
Well...
..you got my number.
And you've got mine.
Yes, I do.
So I'll let you know
how things go...
in New York.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Good.
I've still got some...
Some, like, feelings
to sort through, about...
Bridget?
Yeah.
I didn't forget.
It's "Bridget."
I...
It's...
It's OK.
Is it?
Yeah.
I met someone.
You met someone?
Yeah, I mean, it's not
like we're getting married
or anything, but...
Wait, now I'm... I'm confused.
This...this is someone different?
Not the writer guy?
Yeah, no, a different guy.
A new guy.
A different guy?
What?
I don't...
you know, it's...
Thank you.
So...
Don't.
You'll ruin it.
Get outta here.
I'm sick of you.
Pitch and go. Pitch and go.
Keep up the pace.
It's not a big deal.
I'm sorry.
It actually is quite a big deal.
But don't go too fast.
Ollie, you get really jittery when
you go too fast.
I need to make sure
that you don't speed
through the whole thing
in such a way
that nobody understands
exactly what you're saying,
because we invested
a lot of time...
Jeety.
Jeeto, I need you
to shut up. All right?
This is exactly
what I'm talkin' about.
You're driving me crazy.
So...
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
The baby...
The...
MOUTHS: Client.
The client inputs
the child's data,
and the baby actually
tracks its growth.
So when it's time
to move up to a bigger size...
..there it is...bam...
just on your doorstep.
No hassle. No fuss.
Does the baby have a name?
Yes.
What were we saying
for the baby's name?
Freddy.
Doesn't have to be Fred.
Gabe was another choice
that we came up with.
Gabe the babe.
My point is is that there are
10,000 babies born every hour.
That's 254,000 babies a day.
Somebody's gotta figure out
where to put all that shit.
I wanna be that guy.
10,000 babies an hour.
Wouldn't that be
240,000 babies a day?
Yes.
It was good, Ollie.
You were great.
There was that one little thing,
but I don't think it was a big deal.
How about you?
You think it was good?
Great.
PHONE RINGS
It's mine.
Hey, I'm Jeeter.
How ya doin'?
Hello?
EMILY: Ollie?
Hi.
Are you still
in New York?
Can you hold on one second?
It's bad reception.
I found it.
How does it look?
Looks good.
She was young, huh?
Yeah.
What kind of flowers
did you get?
Blue?
That's perfect.
Today's her birthday.
Talk to me.
I don't know what to say.
Doesn't matter.
All right.
There's...
There's this kid, OK?
And he's in his backyard,
and he's diggin' a hole.
And the neighbour lady
looks over the fence and says,
"What you doing over there,
little Johnny?"
And the kid looks really sad,
And he says,
"Well, my goldfish died,
"so I'm having a funeral
for it."
And the lady says,
"well, that s
an awfully big hole
for a goldfish."
And little Johnny says,
"Well, that's because
he's inside your stupid cat."
You know,
that's terrible.
Thank you.
PA: Final call
for Flight 701 to Los Angeles.
This flight is now closing.
Excuse me. Are you travelling with
us to Los Angeles, sir?
MUSIC: "Hands of Time"
by Groove Armada
# Keep looking through
the window pane
# Just trying to see through
the pourin' rain
# It's hearing your name
# Hearing your name
# I really never felt
quite the same
# Since I've lost
what I had to gain
# No-one to blame
# No-one to blame...
She lives in Los Angeles,
and my work is
in San Francisco,
so that's...
And look, if this
VC money comes in,
we're gonna be swamped
anyway, so...
But it's like,
that's just...
How can I be there for her
if I don't even have my thing
figured out, you know?
I...I can't.
And I was clear with her
right from the top that...
Like, the first day
that we met,
I told her that I had to
have my things,
my work and stuff,
that...
So you won't
be traveling with us
to Los Angeles, then?
No.
OK.
Hi.
I'm Jeeter.
I'm Natalie.
Nice to meet you, Natalie.
Good to meet you, too.
You know, in about 24 hours,
I'm gonna be rich.
Really?
Yeah.
You from New York?
No. I'm from LA.
OK. Did I mention
I was gonna be rich?
You did, actually.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You like that?
It's...it's interesting.
Natalie, what would you do
with 6.2 million, hypothetically?
Should we check it?
Check it.
DIALLING TONE
Does it work?
There's dial tone.
Maybe we should call them.
No. They said Friday afternoon.
It's still Friday afternoon.
But it's not Friday
afternoon in New York.
Seriously, we should
just give 'em a call.
They'll call.
We don't wanna look desperate.
RINGS
Hello? Diaper...
It's not...which...
Hello? There...
Hello?
Diaperush.
This is Oliver speaking.
Yeah.
Right.
Right. OK, so...
we'll talk to you
next week, then.
Thank you.
We got it.
Oh! Oh! We got it, baby!
We got it!
Oh, yes!
Yes!
That was one special lady.
I'm gonna miss her.
Well, no-one can say
we didn't try, right?
Just need the keys.
Oh. Yeah.
Hey, can I hang on
to the key chain?
They're, like, 25 bucks.
You serious?
Yeah.
Aw, keep it.
Thanks.
Yeah.
You, uh, need a ride?
Just gonna clear some stuff
out of my office.
This was fun.
Hey, you come to LA,
give me a call.
Yeah, definitely.
MUSIC:
"Look What You've Done" by Jet
# Take my photo off the wall
# If it just
won't sing for you
# Cos all that's left
has gone away
# And there's nothing
there for you
# To prove
# Oh, look what you've done
# You've made a fool
of everyone
# Oh, well,
it seems like such fun
# Until you lose
what you had won
# Give me back
my point of view
# Cos I just can't think for you
# I can hardly hear you say,
"what should I do?"
# Well, you choose
# Oh, look what you've done
# You've made a fool of everyone
# Oh, well, it seems like such fun
# Until you lose what you had won
# Oh, look what you've done
# You've made a fool of everyone...
Does the artist
ever come in here?
Most days.
You just missed her, actually.
# Cos all that's left
has gone away
# And there's nothing there
for you to do
# Oh, look what you've done
# You've made a fool of everyone
# Oh, well, it seems like such fun
until you...
Hi. Back again?
Yep.
# Oh, look what you've done
# You've made a fool of everyone
# A fool of everyone
# A fool of everyone. #
Chris.
Not so far. Just come back...
there you go.
GUITAR PLAYING
# I guess this time
you're really leavin'
# Heard your suitcase say goodbye
Just don't say anything,
cos I'll lose my nerve.
# As my broken heart
lies bleeding
# They say that true love,
it's suicide
# You say you cried
a thousand rivers
# Now you're swimmin'
for the shore
# You left me drowned in,
in my tears
# And you won't save me anymore
# I pray to god you give me
one more chance, girl
# I'll be there for you
# These five words I swear to you
# When you breathe,
I wanna be the air for you
# I'll be there for you
# I'd live, and I'd die for you
# Steal the sun from the sky for you
# Words can't say what love can do
# I'll be there for you. #
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
MAN: You suck!
I know you like Bon Jovi, so...
I don't.
Emily...
I'm flat broke.
I don't have a job.
I don't have a plan...
And I know I'm...
I know I'm probably
six years too late...
But will you give me
strike one back?
You're married.
I'm engaged.
Do you wanna come in?
No. I think I need the air.
I'm...
I have to get the baby.
I'm sitting
for Michelle.
You sound really good.
Well...
Guess when I'm an old man,
I'll never have to wonder,
"What if...?"
MAN: So how long
have you had this place, Ben?
Going on four years,
but I still have
a lot of plans for it.
WOMAN: Oh, I'm sure Em would be
happy to help you with those plans.
I'm sure she will.
MUSIC: "Breathe (2 AM)"
by Anna Nalick
# 2am and I'm still
awake writing a song
# If I get it all down on paper,
it's no longer inside of me
# Threatenin' the life it belongs to
# Cos you can't jump the track
# We're like cars on a cable
# And life's like an hourglass
glued to the table
# No-one can find
the rewind button, girl
# So cradle your head in your hands
# And breathe
# Just breathe
# Oh, breathe
# Just breathe...
This is a phase
that I'm glad you grew out of.
I don't even recognise you.
Ugh! That skirt.
Oh, those are great boots.
Do you still have those?
Not the boots.
Well, what am I looking
for here? The guy?
No, not the guy.
Whatever happened to that guy?
The photos.
They're from before we met.
Before you and who met?
Me and Oliver.
What are you talking about?
He took them before
I even saw him,
So he did make
the first move.
Kind of.
You ready?
I gotta go.
I'm gonna stop by tomorrow, OK?
I'll help you move.
Where you going?
Michael needs a new suit.
I can't let him shop alone.
Talk. Tell me.
Do I look fat?
Seriously. The pinstripes,
they make me look fat?
Michael,
this is the seventh suit
you've tried on today.
What do you want me to say?
It's a suit.
Oh, I just need
some, you know, give
in the shoulders.
I just need a little...
They do alterations.
Move.
BABY SHRIEKS
Yeah.
Shirts, huh?
That's a nice shirt.
Look at this one.
Shirts.
SALESMAN: Those legs,
they go all the way
to the floor.
Here.
Socks. Yeah.
We about done here?
Hold on now.
We don't want
our pants falling down
in the middle of "I do."
Nobody wants to see that.
Thought you quit smoking.
I did.
What's goin' on, Em?
Oh, all right,
what are you doing?
I don't care.
You have to wait.
Mom!
What?
Have you seen my tie?
Did you look in your room?
Yes. I don't know
where it is.
You better find it.
Is that my tie?
Mom.
What?
Graham took my tie.
Why would he take your tie?
I don't know.
Why? Give it to me.
Hi. I've been trying
this number all morning,
And I was just wondering
if you could find out
If there's something
wrong with the line
or if it's been disconnected
Or if I can make
an emergency breakthrough.
She's sleeping.
OK. OK. Thanks anyway.
Is everything packed?
I brought the minivan.
I'm not moving.
What's going on?
Ben and I broke up.
Honey.
Are you OK?
Why didn't you call me?
What happened?
I had to do this.
OK.
We are gonna sit down,
and we are going to take
a deep breath.
It's gonna be fine.
It is so natural
to be nervous before
you get married.
Do you remember me?
Don't worry.
Ben is gonna understand.
You just need to talk to him.
Just set a time to meet.
Tell him you
need a day or two
to think things over.
I have to call Oliver.
Oliver?
Who doesn't have call waiting?
Sweetie.
I have to talk to him.
I have to tell him
I'm not getting married.
Stop. Give me the phone.
I saw him.
You saw who?
Oliver.
Emily...
He's getting married.
When?
Hi. I have a phone number,
and I was wondering if
you could give me the address
That goes
with that phone number.
What are you gonna say?
I'm gonna say
I broke it off with Ben.
I'm just gonna tell the truth.
Oh, no, no.
I wasn't speaking to you. Sorry.
OK, you ready? Here it is.
I forgot the number.
Find the number.
Hold on. I'm looking.
I'm looking.
She's looking.
Big day.
Hey.
Are you ready, gentlemen?
Ready? Yeah.
All right.
Let's get started.
Hello?
HUBBUB
WOMAN: Honey, are you OK?
Shall I call a doctor?
I'll get somebody to help you.
Go get somebody to help her.
Call 911.
Just get her some ice...
Are you OK?
I got it. I got it.
I'm sure there's a doctor...
I got her. It's fine.
OK.
You OK?
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
I'm so sorry. I have to go.
Excuse me. Are you here
with the ice?
How did you find me?
I had your number,
and I just...
I called information
and got your address.
Wow. Information sure gives out
a lot of information.
I got this.
It's good, thanks.
Is your head OK?
WHISPERING:
Ollie, we're waiting on you, son.
Yes.
You should go.
I'm gonna go.
Oliver.
OK.
Emily.
No.
It's too late.
I'm too...
MUSIC: "Brighter Than Sunshine"
by Aqualung
# I never knew what love...
Oliver!
What's going on?
You're not too late.
I'm not getting married.
My sister is.
You're such a dick.
# Tied up in ancient history
# I didn't believe
in destiny...
Let's go. Let's start without him,
you guys. Come on.
Let's go.
Don't.
You'll ruin it.
# What a feeling in my soul
# Love burns brighter
than sunshine
# Brighter than sunshine
# Let the rain fall,
I don't care
# I'm yours,
and suddenly you're mine
# Suddenly
# Suddenly you're mine
# And it's brighter
than sunshine
# I never saw it happening
# I'd given up
and given in
# I just couldn't take
the hurt again
# What a feeling
# I didn't have
the strength to fight
# But suddenly
it all seemed so right
# Me and you
# What a feeling
# What a feeling in my soul
# Love burns brighter
than sunshine
# It's brighter than sunshine
# Let the rain fall
# I don't care
# I'm yours
# And suddenly you're mine
# Suddenly you're mine
# And it's brighter
than the sun
# It's brighter than the sun
# It's brighter than the sun,
sunshine. #