Please, be very careful.
Hello?
We could just elope, you know.
But then you wouldn't get to see me
dressed like an extra for "Dynasty".
- So much to do...
- Your hair looks perfect, madam.
When I want your opinion,
I'll give it to you.
- Madam?
- That one.
Thank you, madam.
I need a cigarette.
Are you ready?
Almost...
I'm working.
20 minutes before our
engagement party starts?!
Where is my husband?
In the garden, madam.
And where is my coffee?
Coming, madam.
Did the dress fit Tala?
She didn't stop eating
at lunch.
Like a glove, madam.
I love you...
Bye Tala.
Bye.
And Lamia? Did you
take in her clothes?
By 2 cm, madam.
Excellent.
Let's hope this is the
final engagement party
your father has to
throw for your sister.
For a man of his stature
to endure the shame...
How do I look?
You could cover your
shoulders a little more.
It's not cold.
It's not proper.
Did Zina like the green dress
I picked for her?
She loved it, madam.
"Wear this. No black for your
sister's party. Mama"
The cake, how does
the cake look?
Careful!
It looks perfect, madam.
Just perfect.
She'll do it before dinner.
No way, Tala loves
her food too much.
The last time she broke
the engagement before dinner.
And the first time
she waited till Reema had
a mouthful of coffee.
I just hope she keeps
the jewelry this time
8 karats, D flawless.
Who wouldn't?
Tala never keeps
the jewelry.
She's always had
a screw loose.
And how is
my favourite niece?
Uncle Ramzi!
Hello.
You managed to get
on a plane?
Plane?!
You know I'll never
get on a plane!
Not after
that dream I had.
- Yes, yes, uncle.
- The crash, the devastation...
The dream was in 1967...
Right after The Six-Day War.
Israel has a lot to answer for.
Anyway, i wouldn't have
missed it.
I wanted to meet the man
who made it this far, again.
Uncle, I love him.
Of course you love him,
he's Christian and he's rich.
Not to mention:
kind, thoughtful
and forward-thinking.
And handsome.
Handsome is good.
But ask your auntie
why she married me.
Looks and character
come and go;
only large sums of money
last forever.
So it would seem.
You look amazing, sis.
Wish I could say the same.
That's because I've been alone with
mum and Lamia for four whole days.
You know,
I think I've found those weapons
of mass destruction Bush was looking for.
How clever of him to disguise them
as two Arab housewives.
Zina, that dress looks
beautiful on you.
Mama said you should be
entertaining your guests.
Yeah, Tala.
Surely you should be familiar with
engagement party etiquette by now...
She looks so happy,
doesn't she, Reema?
Of course.
And beautiful.
Just like her mother.
No, no, no.
No, I don't think so.
I understand what you're saying,
but I think that 10%
is the maximum
you can expect from that...
Don't worry, we'll talk
tomorrow, OK? Goodbye.
I thought you'd gone
for the day.
The printer's not working
at home.
What are you printing?
Umm, just some
bits and pieces.
Come on.
Come up.
Sit down.
You have a minute,
don't you?
All this is going to be yours
one day, you know?
All of it?!
And your sister's.
But sales are everything.
They're the lifeblood
of this place.
You know I'm not good
at selling, dad.
You don't sell
life insurance...
I know, I know:
"It sells itself."
Life insurance is a sure bet.
I just ask my client:
"Do you know
you're going to die?"
There is only one answer.
Then I ask him:
"Are you 150%
absolutely positively happy
that your wife and your kids are
properly taken care of?"
You've got him.
Come on, try it.
Dad...
Oh, come on.
I'm your client.
Try it.
I'm sorry, dad.
I'm good with the admin,
and Yasmin's better with people.
She's a waitress!
She's learning so she can start
her own food company!
Three years at university
so she can wash dishes!
She doesn't need
her own company,
she has her own company!
I have a date
with Ali tonight.
I like him.
He's a good boy.
Are you going
to the mosque first?
We're heading into town
to see a friend of his,
then we're having dinner.
It's Friday.
I believe in our religion,
I do, I just...
I don't like to go
when everyone else does.
If you don't go
when everyone else does,
how will they know
you're a good Muslim?
Go on then, but don't be out
too late.
I'm not 16, dad.
I know...
So she's Palestinian,
your friend?
Yes, she lives in London but her
wedding will be back in Jordan,
where I was
for her engagement party,
you remember?
What does Tala do?
I think she has some of
her grandfather's spirit in her.
You know she's recently bought
a company over here?
For an Arab woman from her background
that's pretty unusual.
What's the matter?
Are you nervous?
A bit.
I'm always like that
with new people.
Don't be. Tala's great.
Trust me,
you'll love her.
- Evening.
How long have you and Ali
been dating?
About two months.
And? Does he want
to marry you?
I think he's just waiting for me
to ask him.
Tala, my eldest daughter, is
getting married in six weeks.
And what does
your father do?
Stop interrogating the
poor girl, mama. - Hey...
She's going out with Ali.
Not me.
Tala, meet Leyla.
Hello!
Sorry to break
your British reserve,
but we always kiss
in Jordan.
Usually just before
we slit your throat.
When are you going to stop criticizing
our homeland, Tala?
When everyone else stops
being afraid to.
How do you and Ali
know each other?
He went to school
with my third fiancé.
They were
at Cornell together.
She's had four,
you know.
Fiancés, I mean.
Four?
She's still picky.
I've always liked Namir.
- Mama...
He was a drug addict.
He's from a very
respectable family.
Yeah, and during
our engagement party
I caught him in the bathroom
with white powder on his nose.
You always jump
to conclusions.
Maybe he was trying
to hide a skin blemish.
He had some pock-marks
on one side of his face.
Tala, I've just had
your wedding dress taken in.
Congratulations
on your wedding.
Will it be in a mosque?
A church!
A church.
Not all Arabs are Muslims.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have assumed.
Are you a Muslim?
Yes.
Why?
Tala, what kind of question
is that?
Because she was born
a Muslim.
No, she wasn't.
Weren't you?
She was born a female and
a member of a certain race, and
if she'd been adopted by a Jewish
family, she'd have been Jewish.
Thank God
she wasn't adopted!
What the Middle East doesn't need
is more Jews.
Mama, please don't start
with the anti-Semitism.
Anti-Semitic?!
Who's anti-Semitic?!
I am Semitic,
that's the point.
And yet, the Israelis grabbed
Palestine from us.
And Arab countries
threw out
over a million of Jews.
But the Israelis should be fair
to the Palestinians.
They know what is like
to lose their land.
Now someone's
speaking sense!
True. But we need to draw a line
under the past and move forward.
Your headache medicine,
madam.
I don't have a headache.
But it's seven o'clock, madam.
Well, then I haven't adjusted
to London time yet.
Nice to have met you.
I apologize for my daughter.
- Good night.
- See you.
You didn't answer
my question.
I'm not Jewish.
Why not?
Why aren't you?
I don't subscribe
to any religion.
So you live
without any faith?
Ha!
I didn't say that.
Why should my beliefs
offend you?
They don't.
I just wanna know
why they don't offend you.
Tala, ease up.
Don't they do small talk
in the Middle East?
This is the small talk
in the Middle East.
For a serious debate
we move on to politics.
And before that happens,
I'm gonna take Leyla
to dinner.
Do you wanna blow off your parents
and join us?
They're going back
to Jordan tomorrow.
But thank you... both.
Perhaps another time.
I'd like that.
We can be all British
and talk about the weather.
You are naughty!
Leyla!
He'll be here soon!
Come on!
I don't understand why Ali
can't eat with us first?
He's booked
a tennis court, mum.
At one o'clock?
That's lunch time.
Only in a suburban house though, mum,
I believe London's...
what? 2 hours ahead of us?
Or would that be
two years?
You and your
cosmopolitan attitude.
What kind of salad
are you making anyway?
It's a Greek salad.
Oh, and an Indian salad
isn't good enough for you!
Mum, what is an indian salad?
Week old lettuce and chilies?!
You two are so worried
about other cultures.
London! Greece!
What about
your own heritage?
Did you ever think
about that?!
India has one of the richest
cultures in the world.
Well, I'm glad
you said that, mum.
Coz I'm thinking of spending
6 months out there.
Backpacking.
You are not going backpacking
and in India of all places!
What about the culture,
the heritage?
What about being rapped
and murdered?!
And clean underwear?
Why would you
take underwear, Yasmin?!
What if you meet
people that we know?
They'll think we can't afford
to send you on a real holiday.
Mum, there are like
a billion people in India.
What are the chances that I'm gonna bump
into someone from your Surrey Bridge Club?!
Ali!
Are you going to the door
dressed like that?
We're going
to play tennis, mum.
What's that smell?
Feta cheese.
- Hi.
How are you?
Ali!
- Hi, auntie.
Hello. How are you?
First class.
- Hi, uncle.
- Hello, Ali.
Mmm, something smells good
in here.
Thank you.
That's my Greek salad.
Hey, Yasmin, I didn't know
you could cook.
Of course she can.
And so can Leyla,
who makes the best cakes
and never puts on weight.
Yeah, that's our Leyla.
She's gonna make
a wonderful housewife someday.
And, apparently,
she knows how to sell
life insurance
with the best of them.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
It sells itself.
- We should be going.
- Bye, uncle.
Oh, next time
come for lunch.
Oh, I'd love to,
next time.
- Come.
- OK, OK...
Let's hope she has the sense
to hold onto him.
Like a life raft.
Mum!
Oh, by the way. We're meeting
some friends at the club.
Hope that's OK.
Scared I'd beat you
one-on-one?
Terrified!
Who are you
playing with?
You remember Tala?
Oh, and another
friend of mine, Jeff.
Actually, I owe Jeff a game
so you can play Tala.
Is that OK?
Fine.
Hey, how are
you guys doing?
Hope you've been practicing.
- Yeah, right. - Hey, how are you?
- Not bad, you?
Hello.
Come on, let's play.
How are you?
They have a really
great coach here
if you want a lesson...
That was amazing.
You're pretty good,
y'know?
You're not so bad yourself.
This way.
I'll show you
the changing room.
That was quite a comeback.
I prayed for divine intervention.
Look: I didn't say
that there wasn't a God.
It's just religion
that bothers me.
Sorry if I offended you.
On the contrary,
you made me think.
Yeah? About what?
About... Thank you.
...how we fallow certain paths.
Is it just expectation
or conditioning?
Let me
take a look at that.
It's alright.
I'm always clumsy.
You know you should...
You should really
relax more.
Just be at ease
with yourself.
Maybe a shower will help.
They're over there.
Alright.
So, are you coming
for the polo match tomorrow?
Honey, as much as I'd like to see
you fall on your your ass,
no can do tomorrow.
Rugby's on.
It's just a practice game.
It's usually fun.
I'm supposed to have lunch
with my family tomorrow.
Hey, I'm sure
they won't mind.
Think of all the fun you'll have
turning divots. Just watch where you tread, huh?
You missed lunch yesterday and now
you want to miss it today?!
It's Sunday!
Why don't you ask Ali
to come for lunch?
He could meet grandma.
He's taking me
to a polo match, mum.
Polo?
You mean the game?
No, mum,
she means the mints.
All those horses
and sweating South Americans!
Will prince Charles be there?
Well, at least you're making
an effort for a change.
What's that?!!
Excuse me.
Sure.
- Hello?
- Leyla?
Hi, dad...
Listen, we're gonna be later
than I thought.
Ali's really
into the polo.
- He just called.
- Who just called?
Ali.
He asked if you wanted to go over
to his place to watch rugby
after you got back.
I didn't tell
your mother, daughter.
Thanks, dad.
Thanks, Antoinette.
See you later.
- Hello.
Impressed?
I didn't even
break out in a sweat...
I kept thinking
you were gonna fall
leaning across on a horse
like that.
I like to take chances.
Is that why you left
your family's business?
I wanted to see if I could create
my own brand.
I'm impressed.
No, don't be.
Not yet, at least.
I've yet to get
a decent order.
But something
should pan out soon.
How about you?
Me? Nothing to tell.
My dad encouraged me
to join his company
and I've never left.
And? You like it there?
It's not exactly inspiring.
So what inspires you, Leyla?
Writing... Fiction...
Can I read
some of your stuff?
How else am I gonna find out what
goes on beneath that quiet exterior?
Let's...
Hello?
Really?
You have an amazing talent.
I'm... just learning.
Make sure
you do something with it.
Have you really been
engaged four times?
I mean, you seem like
such a decisive person.
Yeah, well,
I'm not proud of it.
You know about the last guy.
He had a problem with drugs.
Or make-up.
The second guy:
Well, he ticked
all the boxes.
He's Christian Arab, good family,
handsome, intelligent..
It just didn't click.
I can understand that.
And the first?
Well, that was a big mistake I
let my mother pressurize me into.
He produces tons of dates.
My mother loves dates.
You can never have
too many dates.
Oh, trust me,
I found out you can.
How about you? What about you
and Ali? How's that going?
I like him a lot.
Does it click?
Not the way
I imagined it should.
Well, maybe we expect
too much.
It's starting to rain.
Oxford! Oxford's where you go to
get a degree, not to get away.
It's only an hour
by train.
Why do you have to go
for two days?
So if it takes me 3 hours,
I can stay the night?
Oh, my God.
What is that?!
It's Ethiopian bread.
We have Indian bread
right here.
Anyway, I thought
they were starving in Ethiopia.
Yeah, well, if they had bread,
then this is what it would look like.
Who are you going with?
A friend.
Oh, Ali.
No, not Ali.
Does everything have
to revolve around him?
She has a friend and they're going
away for a couple of days.
Why do you make
everything a problem?
Don't let her
get to you, Ley.
She's not...
She's not getting to me.
What's wrong?
Are you two-timing Ali?
Of course not.
You know me,
I can barely go out
with this one guy properly.
Yeah, why is that?
Is there anything you want
to talk to me about?
No.
I mean: anything.
You lied to mum and dad
last week.
About the polo with Ali.
I know. I can't believe
I did that.
No, it was about time
if you ask me.
But why?
Who are you
going to Oxford with?
Nobody.
Just Tala.
Ah, I see...
What?
What do you see?
Well, nothing.
It's just you've been spending
a lot of time with this Tala,
haven't you?
She's nice.
Nice?
'Nice' as in 'mum's bridge club
ladies nice' or 'nice' as in...
'hot'?
What's wrong with you?
Her family's sponsoring
a charity event
and her sister's going
to be there, OK?
OK...
Do you two think that lunch
will make itself?!!
No, but that lettuce has walked
outta fridge on its own.
Come and take
this horrible bread
and send it to Africa
where it belongs!
Have you ever been
to Oxford before?
Oh, I love it!
There's something
magical about it,
especially the buildings.
"That sweet city
with her dreaming spires".
Matthew Arnold?
Mh-mm...
Shall we
go see the library?
I'd love to.
What's Lamia doing?
Buying a picnic hamper.
Is she upset with us?
Just with me.
She wants me to shop
for the wedding.
In Oxford?!
Well, I've refused
to meet her in Paris.
Here, Leyla. Try it.
Mmm, that is amazing.
Lamia, would you like
to try some?
I don't do carbs.
Since when?!
Lamia, you used
to study here, right?
Mhm.
What subject?
Flower arranging.
So... I hear you
didn't get the order.
Well, maybe now you can
come back and help dad
and stop all this
independent stuff.
You know, Leyla is
the most brilliant writer.
You have to read
her stuff.
No, no. I'm just
learning. But I do love it.
One day soon you will read
her stuff in bookstores.
Could you publish an edition
with pictures in it?
Shall we walk
some more?
- No.
- Yes.
Whatever you prefer.
I need to get back
to the room.
Kareem always checks
where I am.
Tell him
that you're busy.
Are you coming
with me?
No. Come on.
It's exactly that kind of relationship
I wanted to avoid
at all costs.
So your fiancé
is not like that?
Hani? No.
He is an Arab and he's born
and brought up in Jordan.
But he's different
from the rest.
Kind, open-minded.
And he makes
a great martini.
He sounds wonderful.
Yeah, he is.
He is.
At least I can't find
anything wrong with him.
Why are you trying?
Thank you.
For what?
For all this.
It's overwhelming.
You know, it's been a while since
I've seen it all through new eyes.
Thank you.
I have absolutely
no sense of rhythm.
Come here.
What are you thinking about?
Why I didn't meet you
years ago.
We'd have been underaged.
Hello. Hi Hani. I'm fine.
Can I call you later?
No, nothing's wrong.
I just woke up.
I'll call you in a while, OK?
Bye.
[whispering:]
Yeah, I love you too.
Have you ever
done this before?
Slept with a woman when my fiancé
makes wedding preparations?
No.
Never done that before.
That's not
what I meant.
When I was 18, I fell
madly in love with a girl
in my first year in college.
We spent few wonderful
months together.
I never knew
I could feel so
complete...
So alive...
'Till now, obviously.
'Till now.
So, what happened?
I broke it off.
I was in pieces.
I told myself that
it was for the best.
That I was away from home and
I was lonely and...
And now?
This is not a way
to live, Leyla.
It's not easy.
It's not acceptable.
We didn't break any rules
last night, Tala.
Yeah, but we did
where I come from, OK?
Nobody lives like this.
At least not openly.
And you live in the West now.
Yeah, but I don't think it's acceptable
to cheat on you fiancé
anywhere in the world.
What do you like most
about this place?
Worlds that once existed.
Just the scent of antiquity.
Ugh, smells like mould in here.
I don't care
what anyone says, Lamia.
You have a romantic soul.
Hello, mama.
Can you hear me?
Stop the drier.
- Hello, Lamia.
- Mama.
Your tea, madam.
This place is
a complete dump.
Give it to Philippe.
Only museums
and no shops.
They don't even
have a Gucci!
Did you get her
something colourful?
Tala thinks
grey is a colour.
And they got bored
of shopping.
They?
Her friend is here with her.
Leyla.
The Indian Jewess?
The Indian.
I didn't know
she was Jewish.
They're spending
all their time together.
I guess it's nice for Tala
to have such a close friend.
Good thing she's coming back
next week, huh?
That's the other thing.
I think she wants to stay in London
a while longer.
She did this
with the second engagement.
Or was it the first?
And she never came back
for the wedding.
I'm sure it's not
exactly like that.
Mama? Mama?
Home, sweet home.
Hello?
Mama!
Hello, my love.
- Hani!
- Did you enjoy your trip?
Yes.
I miss you. I'd give
anything to be with you now.
Sit down. Sit down.
I have a surprise for Tala.
I'd like you to see it.
How was your trip?
Fine, I just walked in.
I know.
How do you know?
I can see you.
What do you mean?
Where are you?
Right here.
Sweetheart...
They're so in love...
It brings tears
to my eyes.
And you must be Leyla.
It's such a pleasure
to meet you.
Tala's talked
about you a lot.
You too.
How was Oxford?
Lovely, much more
than I'd expected.
You know, no one ever says
how romantic Oxford is:
the river, its buildings, the history...
Well, let's have dinner.
You girls must be hungry.
I have to go
but thank you.
Oh no,
I won't hear of it.
A quick bite.
Hani works in the Jordanian
gorvernment, you know?
The foreign office.
Does that cover
relations with Israel?
Yes.
How can you stand it?
We have to stand it.
And sometimes even learn
something from the Israelis.
What do you
want to learn?
How to shoot children?
Obviously not that.
But Israel is the closest thing
to a democracy
that we have
in the Middle East.
Oh, thank God I didn't send your
sisters to that American school.
They turned you
into an Arab-hater.
Auntie,
your daughter is one
of the proudest Palestinians I know.
Why don't you show
Leyla & Tala the invitations?
What invitations?
To our wedding.
Well?
It's beautiful.
Really perfect.
Are you alright?
Just a headache.
Here.
I just need a bathroom.
Upstairs.
Ninth door on the left.
Thank you.
Do you want me
to go with you?
No, I'm fine.
What are you doing?
Holding your hand.
So what happens?
We get 5 min
of hand-holding?!
I get the night in Oxford
and he gets the night in London?!
That's not fair.
What is fair, Tala?
We can't live like this.
Our families won't understand.
I can't lead you
into a life that's...
...difficult.
I don't need
your protection.
Thanks to you,
I know what I want
and I can't go back.
I want to feel the way I did
last night every day.
I want to be with someone that
ten years from now
makes my heart jump
when I hear
her key in the door.
And that someone is you.
I...
I can't hurt Hani.
Are you in love with him?
There are things
I love about him.
I can't ruin lives.
You will.
Especially yours.
Tala, are you OK?
Tell me you can do this.
Tala...
- Ramzi, welcome!
- Hello.
Christ, I'm still here.
No two women should look this
beautiful at six in the morning.
Is the King coming
for breakfast?
No, I'm going
to the airport.
Sami's flying in from New York
for the wedding.
I haven't seen
your brother in years.
Does he still like musicals?
I don't know.
But I'm sure he's looking very
much forward to seeing you.
Why?
We'll be back in time for breakfast
with your parents.
Wasn't he supposed to get a place
for Lamia like 4 years ago?
Would you leave a suite
at the best hotel in town
if you were getting it for free?
I'd leave Paradise itself
if mama was there.
Well, Kareem would brave Hell
to secure his enheritance.
He's not their son.
But in the absence of a son he
is the perfect son-in-law.
Which David could never be.
Anyway, he broke up with me.
He did? I'm sorry, sweetheart.
He wants to bring up
his kids as Jews.
Hanukkah, Passover...
Imagine mama's face...
I'd really rather not.
Though it might be worth it.
We thought we could start
our own mini peace process.
He never made a secret of being
attached to his culture.
Then why did he even
get involved with you?
I mean, what kind of a person
allows you to
get emotionally entangled
when they know
there's no way forward?
I need a coffee.
No. No...
You need to stop selling
yourself short.
Sometimes... sometimes..
you can't stop and rationalize
everything so perfectly.
Don't you ever
just do something?
Even when you know deep down
it's gonna be a disaster?
You will like Zina,
if you give her a chance.
She's a nice girl.
And she wears
a lot of black also.
I think the two of you
will match perfectly.
I'm really not interested in women.
Too busy working at
the investment bank, I imagine?
I mean, you have to start thinking
about your future, Sami.
What? Like you?
Yes.
Like me.
Welcome, Sami.
Thank you.
It's not very often that I have
all my daughters at home at the same time.
I'd like to propose a toast.
To Tala and Hani!
And may you have
many daughters.
Oh, papa!
No thanks, I'm vegetarian.
Really?
Me too.
Have you ever been to "Dan's Bakery"
in New York?
In the Village?
I love that place.
They make the best
Arabic bread.
And they have
the best looking bakers.
That's not important,
daughter.
Well, it is to me.
Did anyone see?
There was another
suicide bomb last night.
It's barbaric the way
they brainwash these people.
This idea of Paradise
waiting for you
if you kill innocent people.
They're not killing
innocent people.
They're killing Israelis.
Have you forgotten
what they did to us at Sabra
and Shatilla and Deir Yassin?
So we sink to their level
and kill children?
Children who grow up
to be Israeli soldiers.
Kareem, please...
With all due respect, Hani,
but you and I have never suffered
like our Palestinian countrymen.
If I remember rightly, you were busy
the last time we went to a refugee camp
to interview people for jobs.
I was holding the fort at the office
for your father that day.
And Lamia and I went to the refugee
charity dinner just last month.
Where the refugee's
washed the dishes.
Will you all excuse me please,
I have a...
I've got a lot I have to do.
The seamstress
will be here at 10.
Make sure you hold
your stomach in this time.
Are you trying to kill me,
creeping into the house
like a robber?
Sorry.
You missed "Bollywood Sisters".
Nina's just found out
her 16 years old daughter
is pregnant and a drug addict.
I made you some pasta.
I need to talk to you.
What's the matter?
Are you sick?
No, I'm fine.
Actually very good.
Happy.
Where's dad?
In town with a client.
He'll be back home soon.
Ali called.
Oh, shit, I forgot about him.
Well, he's a wonderful boy.
Mum, I'm not happy with him.
Then auntie Gulshan's son
is looking for someone.
He's very successful.
He's a bookie!
And tall and handsome.
He's 6 foot 7!
All I can see is his navel.
Well, then you'll have
tall children.
Mum, I can't be
happy with him!
The way I'm
not happy with Ali.
And I've always
known why but
I was hoping that the reason
I thought was the reason
might not really be the reason,
and that things would change,
but they never have,
not really, and now
I know for sure that
what I've been feeling all these years
is actually the right thing
and there's nothing wrong with it...
- Do you want cheese with it?
- Mum, what I'm trying to say is...
- I haven't got cheddar for pasta, parmesan though...
I've got olive oil...
- Just listen to me, I'm gay!
I'm home.
What did I miss?
I'm gay...
But I've only been gone
two hours...
You always said you just
wanted us to be happy.
I lied.
Who did this to you?
I haven't caught
a disease, mum,
I'm just gay,
like I have brown hair.
First you stop coming
to mosque,
now you're
up to your neck in sin!
It's not a sin!
Mum, I haven't killed or stolen
and I'm trying not to lie to you.
It's a huge sin!
According to who?
According to God!
What kind of a God is that?
I don't accept it!
Then you will burn in Hell!
That's enough!
It's OK.
Nooo!
I think maybe it's time we discuss getting
you that flat you've been asking for.
If I could help it, I would,
but I can't.
I know, daughter.
I know.
How many pre-wedding dinners
is it possible to have?
And another thing, if the rule's
"no black", then fine...
but how come you get a dress
that's elegant
and I get one
that's Liberace?
Because I did Tala's shopping
for her in Paris.
"Zina, don't wear black,
it's not a funeral. Mama"
It is a funeral for the 20 lambs that got
slaughtered for this dinner.
They made tofu kebabs
for you, sweetheart.
Come on, Zina.
Sami's downstairs.
He asked where you were.
Send him this dress,
he'd probably love it.
What kind of a stupid
comment is that?
He likes you a lot,
you know.
Yeah, well,
I like him too.
You should go out
with him.
He's the right age
to marry.
You seem to have
a lot in common.
You both like New York,
you both like black clothes...
We both like men.
Stop saying things like that.
Yeah, if you don't say it, Z,
maybe it won't be true.
Kareem thinks it's a phase.
If he meets the right girl,
he'll get over it.
That strategy sure didn't work
for uncle Ramzi.
Uncle Ramzi is not gay!
Yeah, and the Pope
ain't Catholic.
What do you think, Lamia?
Do you think that...
Do you think that
being gay is a "phase"?
Do you think it's alright
to sacrifice your own sister
to a life of misery-marriage
to someone who's gay?
No matter how well
their clothes match?
Well, I guess you would know more
about that than anyone else.
What's her problem?!
I have a strange sense
of déjà vu.
I'm sorry, papa.
Have you told Hani?
I don't know
what to tell him.
Except that I know it won't be fair to him
to go through with the wedding.
You know what fathers want
for their daughters?
For them to be happy.
Sons move on,
they have choices.
Especially here,
in the Middle East.
But a daughter...
A daughter needs a hand
now and then.
What are you gonna do
about this?
Oh, I don't know...
Maybe we can just
have the party.
Your uncle Ramzi can tell
his plane crash stories.
And everyone in town can toast
to new scandal with champagne.
See Hani.
Go and get dressed.
It'll be OK.
Ravi.
Sir?
Pack all the wedding food
and send it to the camps.
They should have
cancelation insurance for weddings.
That stuff would sell itself.
Can I have the keys, dad?
She won't get it.
Get what?
Nothing.
Where are you going?
I'm having Leyla look for flats.
She doesn't have to go.
She needs to.
What exactly happened?
I broke Hani's heart.
Hey, Tala. You have to
give yourself a break.
If you knew
he wasn't the right one
then you did
exactly the right thing.
Yeah, except I should've
told him sooner.
Look, honey, we all wish
we had far-sight.
So what about you, huh?
Me? YFS.
Young, Free & Single!
You're not seeing Leyla?
Neah, she dumped me.
What happened?
Well, on the plus side
it wasn't really my fault.
She told me she's gay.
I know, I was shocked too.
You know, she even
told her parents.
- You're kidding?!
- No.
You got to admire
her guts.
She's always had
a fearless streak that one.
You know, there's not many people in
our community that'd be willing to do that.
Always liked that about her.
Come on, you.
Hello?
Hello. This is
Tala speaking.
Can I speak to Leyla?
Ah, yeah.
One minute.
For you.
Who is it?
Tala.
I'm not talking to her...
Yasmine...
Yasmine... I'm not talking to her.
Take the phone.
She can't come
to the phone right now.
No, I'll...
I'll call back tomorrow...
Perhaps one of the most stunning
archaeological finds of that century,
indeed any century,
was the finding in the south of
Jordan of the Lost City of Petra.
Dramatically carved out of frozen
coloured stone by the Nabataeans,
the massive columns of the temples
rise up to surprise visitors
as they walk through a high canyon
to reach the entrance.
A breathtaking sight.
Now a thriving turist destination,
Petra has enthralled generations of
archaeologists and visitors alike,
thanks to the stories
and beauty of its Lost City.
Like the rest of Jordan,
it is well worth a visit.
She's good.
- Hello.
-Naturally, it's much...
Oh, it was so great to go...
Apparently, you can only get
into Petra on a horse or a camel.
- That would be a great laugh.
- It would be fun.
What are you doing here?
My family sponsored the lecture.
I'm interested in Jordan.
It has a population of 5 million
and no natural resources
to speak about.
Petra's lovely but there isn't much
to say about Jordan...
because it's me you're interested in.
How was your wedding?
Leyla, let's go.
This is my friend Jennifer.
Your friend?
Her girlfriend.
Girlfriend...
Who was that?
That's my friend Tala,
her family...
Do you want that?
Do you wanna join us
for a drink tonight?
I can't, I have to work.
Yeah, how's that going?
I got the order.
That's fantastic, Tala.
Great! Do you know how difficult is
to get into those big chains?
Thought that's exactly
what you wanted?
Yeah, it was.
Well, we should celebrate.
It'll be fun.
Leyla said she might
join us tonight.
No, I'm...
I'm really busy.
Is everything OK?
I don't get it.
Which part?
Why do you wanna
get Leyla & Tala together?
I mean, the other day Tala
didn't seem interested at all.
Listen. Did you ever watch
the TV show
"The L Word"?
No... But did you ever consider
not talking in riddles?
They're in love
with each other.
Who?
Sonny and Cher!
Leyla & Tala.
Leyla & Tala?!
- Good evening, madam.
- Evening.
I'm meeting Ali.
The other party
hasn't arrived yet.
Would you like
to take a seat at the bar
or would you like me
to show you to your table?
- The table.
- Sure.
Oh, good evening.
Reservation for Ali,
7:30.
Oh, yes, follow me.
There you go, madam.
Thank you.
The gentleman sends
his regrets, ladies.
He's unable to make it.
But he does wish you
a pleasant evening at his invitation.
Thank you.
We've been set up.
So it seems.
You look wonderful.
So do you.
I know.
I'm just joking.
How's your husband?
I don't have one.
I broke off the wedding...
the morning of the wedding.
That must've been very difficult.
It was the second hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
What was the first?
Leaving you to go back to Jordan.
Wow, I'm glad to see
you were discreet.
Well? How did it go?
Their eyes met.
A brief smile played
across Tala's mouth.
Unconsciously,
Leyla licked her lips.
It's all over.
OK. I'm still getting used
to the idea.
You sound just like my dad
when you say things like that.
You know what?
I've always liked your dad.
What about you?
How are you?
Fine.
Really good.
My book got published.
Really?
I mean... it will.
Next week, actually.
That is so wonderful, Leyla.
No one deserves it
more than you.
How's your girlfriend?
Jennifer?
Has it been more than one?
No.
She's fine.
Thanks for asking.
Do you love her?
There are things I love about her.
And is that
good enough for you?
No, not really.
Did you tell your parents why you
broke off your wedding?
I told them it wouldn't be
fair to Hani.
Did you tell them why?
Look, Leyla, you...
you don't understand.
Jordan.. it's an
unforgiving place.
My parents have a strong place
in that society and
it's a culture
that doesn't change.
And I guess as long as people don't dare
to be truthful about who they are
it never will change.
Leyla, I love you.
It's that simple.
Why should it be anyone else's business,
even my family's?
We make it their business
every time we have to lie about
who we're with
and why we're with them.
You know,
you once told me
to be more at ease
with myself.
Thanks to you, I am.
Now I'm telling you
the same thing.
"Every night I empty my heart,
but by morning it's full again.
Slowly, droplets of you seep in
through the night's soft caress.
At dawn I overflow
with thoughts of us
and aching pleasure
that gives me no respite.
Love cannot be contained.
The neat packaging of desire
splits asunder,
spilling crimson through my days,
long, languishing
Days that are now bruised
tender with yearning,
spent searching for a fingerprint,
a scent, a breath you left behind."
Rani, where's my parents?
They've just finished lunch, miss.
I gave madam some mint tea.
Go in.
Maybe I should try
a South American maid.
As long as it's a Third World Country,
I don't mind where it is.
They work hard.
They don't even think about...
Mama, papa, I have something
I need to tell you.
What are you talking about?
You're a disgrace.
Haven't you shamed
us enough already?
Please, Reema...
Tala...
Tala, wait.
"The sun hit her hand
with a red hot force
that burned straight through
the clear-veined skin of her wrist.
And when she shut her eyes
tightly and briefly against it,
the heat still glowed
under eyelids like coals."
Thank you, Leyla, for a very
illuminating talk and reading.
If anyone would like
a signed copy,
Leyla has kindly agreed
to do a signing.
I really loved it.
Especially the ending.
That's nice to hear.
Most people just love it
when it ends.
Thank you.
Hi, Amina please.
Amina...
Quite an unique name.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Who should I make it out to?
To Tala...
who finally had the courage
to come out to her parents.
Thank you.
What did you tell them?
I told them I was in love
with a beautiful,
intelligent,
talented,
clumsy
woman.
Sorry we had to go
to a hotel last night.
We won't from next week.
I'm getting my own place.
Congratulations. Is it a flat?
One bedroom.
What is it?
I was just thinking.
You're gonna need
a bigger place.
Why?
Because...
I told my parents
we're gonna have children...
One day... Soon...
Children?!
Soon.
She's what?
But some of my best friends
are Lebanese?!!