Good day, Reggie.
Good day, Esa.
? Today, the? Wonderful day.
It was treated like family? Ino.
He knows ?, what does this mean?
She was very well paid? Ana. Now
I re? e? ? After? Wait, I'm talking about.
Now we re? E? ?
I said after? Why!
Strawberries are inside.
One you missed.
This child?
Euler's formula says,
that? s cut of? e? surface? ino sphere
on the side edges and peaks,
and if the F Number of pages
E Number of edges and V Number of peaks
Always give?
Reggie Kipper?
V? E + F = 2nd
It's no.
The same applies to the pyramid with five
surfaces, four triangles and square.
Minus eight edges, five peaks.
And, for each different combination of
the edges of the sides and the peaks.
Euler was quite thorough.
? Thank you, Mr. Kipper.
See further, Mr. Kipper.
As I spoke,
Consider functions.
Follow the rules and succeed
you will. You will not be betrayed?
The task of bring through Friday.
By Friday.
Janis,? Hi. Here Eleanor.
Dennis is there?
No, sino? S not in? El home.
Do not worry about me.
I thought it might be in you.
I checked the hallway, there is none.
Have a nice day? I wish. Bye.
? Hi, I am.
It is now 10:30.
Sino? S not in? El home.
I've had enough, Dennis. Enough.
Hello. ? He must?
by Gregg. ? He is mad?
Here you go. ? Thank you. Sorry.
Sorry does not mean no ?.
In Service? Will come true slow.
"Only? Ati in mature breast
my dear.
Ve? Do you feel you are,
when it is not? Do you lifted and dropped ?? Ajo.
Ve? Do you awake in a sweet unrest.
Business? Ati her gentle breath.
For several nights to live or die. "
? Hi.
You sino me? I called you?
I was in the "Curbieju". Stolen
my phone. You think ??
Also, you mad. How? Ele me?
They stole my phone.
Be right back. Come on.
Do not make a scene immediately.
They can not fire me.
Please, go.
Let me explain? ? No? Em
business? ati. ? Come on. ? I've had enough.
I'm a musician.
So? I live. ? Nonsense.
With this deal.
? Domi? Ment? FIG. ? What?
The paper mill work ?. ? Why
we have a performance every weekend?
If salaries INCLUDES ?,
to play, this is not the appearance.
Fuck you. Good.
Eleanor, come on. ? No.
Guitar, I threw out the window.
? What? You better not.
Fuck!
Eleanor, you better not.
Come out,
to talk. Please.
Can we talk? ? No.
? Come out to talk.
Is everything okay? Yeah.
Come to talk.
What's going on? ? Eleanor?
? Later we'll talk. Go.
Not later. Now!
? Go on, please.
Talk to me!
Ven. ? Excuse me.
Sorry. Sorry.
Eleanor, I'm sorry. Sorry.
Eleanor.
Even you, Eleanor. Ven.
Super.
Eat, do not read.
Is flowerbeds called the ar? ? No. Hi? A
it? s three days full of wilted flowers.
Reggie, are you? El in? School
a car? ? No.
What did I tell you?
? I'm crippled, I can walk.
Reggie, the? School and home will? walking
by car. ? I love the air, I breathe.
Let's open the window. Car and Driver
Wait, while those pe? A? I ?.
What? Sauce on it?
Meat? ? No.
Tomorrow I'll talk to girls
in the library? nica. Take off to. ? It is.
Where is the tool?
? She returned to Panama.
Why? ? Because green
tickets. It is not your thing.
We did not say goodbye.
? She told me, let me welcome.
My fault? ? Ve? What?
The universe does not spin around you.
Sometimes something simply
It happens. ? Anything? E that means.
No meat, Reggie. Well, this
brown sauce vegetarian?
Yeah, I told you.
Is it really necessary at this time
recruit weld? when? I am 13 years old.
Twelve. What will happen ?, when I visited
the? father? ? He lived like a bachelor?
Esa is here. ? Eighth go
k h? daughters for one month. ? I know.
Long ago I told you? E said.
? You, yes. Christ, Esa.
Bring me some wine in the bedroom, please.
I watched "Masterchef" and fell asleep.
? Hi, Mom.
How are you?
Kli? Em from the booth.
I know.
I do not know. Linden Street?
How Shelly?
Se? Or ??
Why is it after? Not?
Do not let her do that.
There may not work,
irrespective of the money.
I'm fine, I got fired.
It has accumulated.
When? El Dennis and did the scene.
Well? Em on.
I picked up things and the? La.
I do not know. I'm on? Designed by,
what happened.
Thinking? Ljam to
for some time back home.
For a couple of weeks.
I do not know for how long.
There will not come back.
It would not let me.
Guitar, I threw out the window.
I do not know for how long, mom.
In order to gather money. I have $ 160.
I will not bring a lot of things.
What do you think ?, that I bring? For all
what I have is enough one bag.
Hello? Here I am after and why.
Yeah, sorry.
I have not decided? Contract. Just thinking? Ljam.
For girls of Service? I was.
He says that I can.
OK.
I have to go.
That this is certainly costly.
Okay, I will. I will not worry. Share
Shelly, that should not work there.
Notwithstanding deserve? Ek.
I will also.
Bye.
Courtney! Yeah?
? Eleanor will now spend the night here.
Where to sleep?
? The coffees? U. ? This is not a hotel.
How tiresome.
? Can I stay?
Do not worry. If not this would be? Ka, the
It may be longer. The apartment is hers.
For tonight is fine. Tomorrow I
It is provided. ? Do you really? Yeah.
Litters and I read a book. Early
I got up and tried to find a Service? will.
Here you go. CALL? I have.
Abby friend mentioned it to me.
Agency for slow
Employment. - "Au pair"?
Varu? I ?? s show. Ever
look after the children? ? New Moon? O sister.
Tell that? experience? it
s? uvanjem children or? e with? im.
My friend Abby
work for? How she? S name?
Britain from those programs.
Beautifully dressed, get out there
and bullshit about the experience? gained.
? La I too would a check,
or has it? file, so? ? Thank you.
I'll see you later?
Lock, right?
Due to carelessness. Can this it? Im.
Forget Sal mother.
Sal does not interest me. Mama.
Mom, Sal does not interest me.
Mom, aware of? I.
Aware of? I, when I talk, Mom!
I Kelnarila
and mostly looked after children.
OK. ? As varu? Ka.
Varu? Ka? Yeah.
I worked in a family? Ini.
Would you stated
the recommend the contract? ? No.
They returned to Europe. In Belgium.
You can CALL? Em?
Probably not. I'll try
get the? number, but I doubt it.
I watched the moon? O sister.
Since its birth
to medium? ole.
My mom worked when we were little.
Actually, I have raised.
You can CALL? Ete mother
or sister. To recommend ilo.
It is. Overhead? When permission, please.
Sit there.
? Est? Rk, "at least". - "Are you? Ka".
"Are you? Ka?" ? S T E? K A.
In most? Em event
with effort, great effort.
Are you? Ka. At least.
What?
What do you care where I was.
Spra? I love you mate, where are you at night?
Continuous happens, Dennis.
I told you that I had enough.
And thank you. Because of your
failure I was fired.
What do you think? What?
I will not come back, I told you.
Prior to verify in detail
usually proceed
but I have something perfect for you.
Well? Em to this release.
For the? Right? afternoon. What is true ??
As soon as you can for? Ger.
? This afternoon? Yeah.
There needs? the? live. ? It is.
For slow i ?? show someone.
For a few months, perhaps longer.
What do you think? ? It's okay.
Dru? Ina the Upper West Sid,
care will be? 12-year-old
and carried la? ja
housework. Right? Yeah.
Excellent no. Elect address. Tasks
will it be? a brief interview with his mother.
Along the way buy
bright red ilo
and something lighter? ego for the? i.
This is a straight line? No. Hurry.
Hello. ? Hi.
Barbara Kipper.
? Eleanor Logan.
It is.
Let's chat in the library? Nico.
Comes? from the north? Yeah.
Varu? Ka is unsuitable? Expectancy of? La,
mo? However, the company has in China.
? Ez bad week I will
visited. ? Kadi ?? ? No.
Kadi? Only the balcony.
We have 15 balconies. If ho? E?
smoking, you select one. ? It is.
Do not smoke. ? So, Reggie?
This is what Claire said?
Very little.
? Twelve years old.
Leads? by the? school and home
and to arrange ?, to eat. That's all.
If the? what you need,
Esa will help you. Esa? ? Yes, ma'am?
Jesus. Do not stand
so close. ? Yes, ma'am.
Helena will replace the Töölö.
? Eleanor. ? It? boy? ? No.
If the ho? E? receive him,
Give it to him. Here it is prohibited.
It is.
This is important. He must eat.
If it does not compel ?, will not.
He likes a few things
and it is very picky.
Without meat. Only vegetarian.
Do not j? meat, fish or poultry.
J? only tofu and vegetarian.
When you completed? S today?
? The music has to 16.30.
Excellent no.
She picked it be? at 16:30.
In any case, no? Em,
that pe? a? i to? school or home.
First of all, it's not safe.
Secondly, for the salaries engagement driver.
So we agreed.
Esa imposed Lauro.
? Ez 15 minutes I have mass? O.
I'll take a tablet
and be prepared.
Excuse me? Hello. ? Hi.
Eleanor here.
When? La I get it.
They tell you?
They did not, but did not? not de. The car is there.
I'd rather walk. ? Your mom
You very begin that leads ?.
Despite what my mom
you may say, I agree with him.
Finan's not the deal.
I walked, like every day.
Whether it is de? or the sun. Pika. The end.
It is. ? It is.
Hey. Yeah?
It has? moment?
Eleanor here.
Reggie.
Pleased to meet you. ? The same.
Not these? When? ? It is, but I do not mind.
It was incredible.
? Please? ? How to play ?.
The song will be? Enmark.
? Thank you.
How viola and violin
intertwined? ? It is sad and beautiful.
Who wrote it? ? I.
You wrote it? Yeah.
Surely you in this? E ?. I see that you really
I like to play ?. ? Something I have to? Ethyl.
Would you like to? El,
when will it be? adult?
When I grow up? Yeah.
Yes. Why not?
Why not? Let's see?
First, I would not like con? Al
as a bitter and lonely drunkard.
Not to mention,
that art as a dead language.
Despite what would like to say
or how well it is dead.
The theme? One view. ? It is true.
Bum.
"Douzeper". What is this?
? 120 to? To me.
Not a word. ? And it is crap ?.
Noun, multiplication? Ina,
one of 12 legendary knights.
You should know
game? "Dungeons & Dragons".
If you so true ?.
I can not believe that
one pi? ka? lived here. Sexy is.
This re? E? for each girl
by Wed? a ?.
Yes. Only for superseksi.
Because you confused? Strange
and uncertain. ? Also, g. Freud.
And sure? An, it will not? Never
in? el girls who will have sex with you.
Yeah, right.
It looks delicious. ? What? On
Sauce is this? ? Only eat.
Brown without meat.
? Eat. Vegetarian wok is.
In all he substitutes bovine basis.
Excellent no sounds. I can not
believe how fast you on? la.
This stra me? I.
Mama took me 10 minutes
employed as a weld? when 12-year-old.
As soon as I moved.
Luck he had.
V? Em is this? Ava?
The rich? I they are. Hi? A is large
as? the railway? ka station.
What do you know
to educate 12-year-old?
It has? room, food and salaries on.
What would you? E hotel?
One year you? Lived with Dennis,
12-year-old will not this? Ava. ? It is true.
You might need? CONCLUSION. Kitaro
he threw out the window. ? I did it.
Fuck it. It was completed? Ek.
Goa? Am to be rich? Em.
Bye. ? Bye.
Do not stop.
? Is wonderful. ? No.
Last days is not it? Utim
inspiration for violon? elo.
Here practicing ??
Most? But it? Ka hi? I was.
Acoustics is complete.
Hi? A is incredible.
It was built by Captain
Francis Fowke 1898th
He has designed the Natural History
Museum. Obo? Eval is a large building.
Why is it empty?
Mama wanted to contracting to go handmade
Panel made ?? of ice Mallorca.
There? S likely. As large
the second in-house and, as can be seen ?.
You could swim.
? I do not. I can not swim.
What? Why?
? Nobody? S I? E not learn? Il.
Thus, it is not. I'll learn how clay.
It is very tasty.
Now I know? Erjat.
CALL? Ite, if you need anything.
I'd prefer to eat with us.
? I j? there. ?? strange.
Yeah? I j? itself.
TV viewing schedule.
Sometimes watching "Telemundo".
Perhaps projected? own
concerns and? expectations of it.
In brilliant,
top performance. ? Thank you.
What to? We plan?
What's your? the quartet? el summer?
Somehow I have enough violon? Ela.
You might need? Pause.
Yes. Perhaps it is true.
I will take a break from violon? Ela.
I propose just one week.
Then will it be? continued.
Yes. It has ?.
No one younger? Ego than 75 years
not interested in this great? on antique music.
It's time for Me?
and the? el. ? Not really.
I am not proposing
longer? ego pause.
I think the break
OK. Obsolete it.
Well? Em to talk about it.
Where are you from?
From the Oneidas, New York.
The town near Syracuse.
Of course, you hear? Al'm for it.
I researched for seminar
of pre-war architecture.
I've read about this area? ROM.
Was there a stage ?? ati?
When I was younger? A is.
Perhaps the only way to remember.
Now, all without money
and the unemployed. Leaving ?? one is.
It has? brother or sister?
You have mentioned the elderly? Ego brother.
I also have younger? O sister.
What the? Right? ? Working in a bar.
And brother? ? In the army.
In Afghanistan.
And your parents? I?
Eat your ice cream before it melts.
The decisive? Ite wrote.
It takes into? Quires the final assessment is not.
Seminars departure on Friday.
Not by Petek,
not on Monday, and on Friday?
? Hi. How was it?
I'm glad it's over.
Hate? Im physics. Damn physics!
How was the exam
mathematics? ? Excellent? No.
Why is he so calm?
? Because I did not coalesce? One like you.
Good, good. Who's on the juice?
We have to go.
It travels to your mother.
Where to go now?
? Mind your own business.
Calm down. ? Spra? Perhaps fitting
I love you, when your mother where he was going?
Sorry. ? It's okay.
I'm not trying to be clever.
By car we have. Mama
go to the airplane ?? e? ez one hour.
If raisins, baby?
No, thank you. Would it coffee.
Coffee? There will be zero.
Sorry for the delay.
The alarm clock did not ring.
Good morning, sir? On.
? It is not? Today at camp? When?
Sit down and drink coffee.
The camp is for? Not today, but says,
that no? e to go. ? Must. What, no? E?
He says that no? E.
We'll be late. And I do not even know,
where I have to take. Where?
Relax, I'm not going.
It's not up to you.
Yeah? From whom else?
Your mom
gave me accurate? instructions.
Aja? Yeah. No pametuj, kid.
? Who pametuje? I do not.
Just sit and re? Engagement blood? Loop.
? They do not know not ?.
It seems to me,
that my mother's instructions
not very clear,
because they do not know ?,
when and where you need to go.
? El Be? in the camp.
It does not look so bad.
There will be zero. Why is this
so bad? In the camp it ?.
The nature of the lake.
I would? Like.
Aja?
Camp? S songs,
banal debates
and pointless discussions about the? port,
heroes and action films.
And all of this? E in the bus.
Do not forget? E in logging
canoeing, trails with obstacles
Camp? ki fire
pubertal? s clapper.
Pubertal? Ka gang is fine.
Teenager you.
This is my mother's a bad idea.
Not mine.
You should give her a call.
? That I do not recommend highly.
Let me handle this.
We'll avoid complications.
I am responsible for you.
? Then do the responsible thing.
Be right back.
Sorted.
? How do you think ??
I know this guy.
Everything will be re? Il. ? According why?
He marked? S my name, I challenge
the? ronment? ek. Without question Canj.
After? Sends? him? ek?
? It's okay. The deal we got.
Try to understand. I'm not for camping.
Si la? To? Surely you.
Close is excellent in the restaurant.
It has? like eggs Benedict?
Everything is organic. Come on.
After the Why.
After the Why. After? Wait!
52 dollars for? Pina? No salad?
Goa? S good.
Believe me. Everything is top-notch.
Usually eat ri? Oto with wild mushrooms.
Naro? I? can be anything I pay? I am.
We have opened a bill.
Just lettuce. ? Only that?
Eat. Type is the top global chef.
What are we after? Ela
next? Six weeks?
This is New York, baby.
Not? him to the end, believe me.
This is not right.
It should be in the camp.
Not after? Tion, never.
Enough has been said about the camp.
It is not up to you. ? But it is.
Nobody cares where I am. ? Not really.
I do not think this way,
This is a fact.
The operation is continuing,
whether I am in the camp or reading at home.
Personally, I would prefer to read at home, if it
I cared. And believe me, that is.
And Esa? ? Think ?, that it cares where
I was and what the? German? There's just work.
This is very strange, Reggie.
This is my? Life.
Welcome? Ia? Penis? Ture.
Towards the safety and sanity
Vessels best as I can.
OK.
Hotel am I? E to quit.
What errors? But it ??
? I'd conjured.
I do not play games. Seriously.
Completion of the contract I have with the relationship.
You could talk.
Million're fucked.
Drunk? with the bunch,
You repugnant to me.
Forget it, go home. ? I did
error. Now I know. Talk to.
Because we? E. ? Stop me
the? iljati message? contract. ? Eleanor?
I was desperate, since you from? La.
? Maybe we should think about it.
I wrote a bunch of songs about you.
I would like to make them sing. ? Jesus.
Let's go to drink on,
the "scratcher". Bill is a DJ there.
O? Em talk ??
? Only to drink and talk about.
I do business? A ??
I do, fool.
At the bottom here.
I can not sleep or eat.
If thoughts ?, it is desperately
whimper attractive, is wrong ?.
Farewell. Farewell.
? Eleanor, come on. Please.
Bo? Now this? In other
words will? ? La forward?
No other words.
Exactly these words.
It is. For Guitar
While? salaries ala. Believe me.
Fucking bitch.
What are you here? ? What is happening?
? No ?, come on. ? The payment amounted to ?.
Fucking bitch!
Are you okay? Yeah.
I'm really? Al.
? Would you eat what?
I can cook
vegetable soup with noodles room.
Do curry with tofu. I do not have that? When.
Something needs? eat.
Of course. ? Super.
Film can we look to the end.
If I question this? Daddy,
it such outbursts usual?
Yes. At least I'm not aware of them.
How? On the colossal mistake.
? Life is a series of colossal errors.
Beginner care for you.
? What? Excellent on you.
Well? Em to know? such
things. ? What? No?
My. Messy
details of the end of the link.
Things out of my privacy.
I do not know so well.
You're too young to understand. ? Do not be
so sure? ana. Excellent well understand.
God. ? Over his years here.
Well? Em that does this concern.
Does that thinking? Ment? about it.
I will not be worried.
Do not worry about me. ? Fine.
I can not promise that I will not
thinking? ljal about it. I thinking? Ljam.
Such here.
It is. Can thinking? Ment ?.
? After? Fair.
Seriously? ? What?
? Soft? Yl error master.
He opened the attack.
I have your horse. ? No
important. However, I'll win.
He knows ?, that would have to leave in Sydney
in Australia? Yeah. ? There? will not.
About the? Father's business collapsed with the type
Stanford or some Stanford.
Now I have in karate
camp. ? With the sounds awful.
Why do I think we need karate?
Because of this every so often someone breaking them?
I would like to camp dance hip-hop.
? This would be? Ude? on your profile.
Ple? Show hip-hop and stuff.
? I know what it is. Despair. Do not go.
You can be. Throughout the day sitting?
in the park with sexy varu? when.
Yes, this is the? German all day.
See this? Ednei
? Women on the flyer.
And I think that all of this ?,
beauty? waiting just for you?
The game has? play. ? Sun? No.
Of course, the? E v.
? Smart? Man.
After a few goods racists? Ing
The remark was thrown in the trash.
? Ah-mat. ? Seriously.
Stop dreaming.
"Juicy fruit" sugar-free?
This picture of me is very in? E ?.
Like you.
Please? ? O? I.
Well, since the round.
Ve? about Modiglianiju?
Yes. But I learned.
He died in misery and deprivation
l. 1920 35 years old.
What is a shortage?
? Great rev ?? ina.
At? El by neighbors in the past
stage tuberculosis meningitis.
The bed was
loads of bottles of alcohol
and empty cans of sardines.
His girlfriend Jeanne H? Buterne
It is worried about him.
Cans of sardines
It could be trashed.
It was the ninth month
with other children.
Two days after his death
the jump from the fifth floor of the contract.
These may be some questions? Am? ? Of course.
When did you become so advanced?
I do not know
or I become advanced.
When you know how to read?
? In the 18 months.
I guess then
become advanced.
What are you reading at 18 months?
Mom got me how to read
"All possible? S things" Dr. Seuss.
On the voice? Yeah.
? It was a shock.
It amused by it.
He led me to the fun.
Crazy. Yeah. It is crazy to be
children younger? s two years,
sitting at a table and reading
a pile of drunks "All possible? s things."
Oh, my God.
When? I found the tracks,
that I'm doing math well.
Re? I eval complex
mathematics? no problems.
What? ? The set? I il
seven- and ten-digit? number.
I can tell you kub
almost every? number.
As De? Inclined? Man.
? No. He is autistic.
As seen ?, am I? Vivacious,
extroverted, accessible and talkative.
Of course. ? Not to mention my
and again the beauty. ? Not to mention.
For me, this is all as mother ?? ina.
? Number, playing, composing.
That I was born.
My on? E is supposedly
extremely intelligent.
What the? Not in China?
? Who? ? Your on? E.
No? not after? not in China.
He's dead. Mama was again wedding contract.
? Al me. ? Thank you. It is? E
a long time ago. Three years I was a star.
How did he die?
? Someone was hit.
The Z? Richu.
There driving like a maniac.
It was a concert pianist.
Many traveled.
And he graduated from the Physics
M IT. ? Unbelievable.
Certainly he had this? Ave,
like everyone.
But he likes to idealized level
mythical figures. Better after? Utim.
And apparently a lot of drinking.
People at this begin to.
Si la? To? Come on.
I forgot
how Zani? cooking hurts.
Similarly, the gravel.
Let her ask that you cook
what else? ? No. Pleasant is.
Would you? La in Chinese?
I know for a great pub in the old? Fourth.
? I distracted her, you throw it away.
Excellent no. Go for a walk.
But remain aware Dinner?
No, thank you. Go for a walk.
And a little dessert? No, thank you.
You can clean up? kitchen.
Are you sure? An?
? I thank you. Thank you.
Surely? Yeah.
It is crazy to go underground,
? E is? car and driver.
Yeah? ? Thank you.
Why can not forgive
and They save? trapped? ? A good guy.
Almost never leads anyone.
Thus the river? 'Lives in your car.
Actually,? Living in Crown Heights
with a? one and seven h? ERKO,
having cerebral palsy.
I am indulgent to him.
And go ?? me, if understood ?.
Neither does.
What did I tell you?
Good? ? Unbelievable.
Monosodium glutamate
? Utim the toes.
We'll sleepy. ? Oh, yeah.
And if something about Gerard.
He worked for John Gotti.
Who? ? Gerard, my driver.
He was Gottijev soldier.
Aja? ? Maybe it? S
connected with these people.
You can help.
? When? Em? ? Your case.
I do not follow you.
? In the case with your boyfriend.
Oh, my God. ? You will not know?
cause al this? av. ? Are you crazy?
This is possible after? El.
Stop this.
? You can talk to him.
I appreciate the concern. ? Please suggest.
? I said, do not worry. ? It is.
Jesus.
Come on. ? Where are we going? ? Have a nice day.
Take a walk in the park.
Who knows ?, Lou Hoy Sing?
? Why do not you practicing? violon? ela?
The game? You can on the balcony. ? The first
Chinese immigrant in New York.
When? El l. 1862 Wedding il is
the girl form Ireland, had two daughter daughters.
Take violon? Elo.
If you are not practicing weeks.
I've had enough violon? Ela.
From? RPA me. ? Do not say that.
I do not care violon? Elo.
? It is. And let's go to the park.
In this stinking park
we go every stinking day.
So we? La
in another stinking park.
Would invitation If any of your
a friend that you play?
They played?
Are you not bored? A? my family? be? ? No.
Are you mine? ? No. Just a thought
I have anyone with whom play ?.
Se? Or ?? And why?
? These are not my friends.
I have no friends
I told you. ? Come on.
Barely spoken to me.
?? E they would be open to them, was in? E ?.
A little more should make an effort.
CALL? Iva Raja. Your friend.
? The karate camp is.
Hey!
Would played "foursquare"?
No thanks. ? Come on, Ben.
Uh, this is serious.
We can not know it?
descend into the kitchen.
I think this is just? A.
What's in? E? soup?
Excellent on it. Just talk,
how good it is. ? My specialty.
It's time to change? ? Number.
Good to have you in? E ?.
If you go looking.
God, help.
What ho? E ?, Dale? I'm doing.
Yes.
Since when is there?
Is there anyone with him?
Okay, I will.
Why did not you call before?
We do that? Mom?
I do not understand,
why I did not notice before.
Okay, thank you.
Who was it? ? My Uncle Dale.
Is everything okay? Yeah.
My on? E is sick? Nica?
? What is it?
He's very sick. Because it's a long time,
but it is currently very serious.
What is it? ? Only the seriously ill.
It is connected to alcoholism.
Cirrhosis of the liver? ? That's where I have to.
In Oneido?
Can I help you? ? It's okay.
My friend Sylvia will be watched
you when I'm gone. ? Of course.
Well? Em to call your mom
and cause stress to go. ? Of course.
Is that right?
Why would not it?
I do not know. I do not know Sylvie.
? Super. It's okay.
I'll be back? Ez 48 hours. ? It is.
You can follow the rules and CALL? Em
Agency, a no? em drama.
I also not. It's okay. Do not worry.
Well? Em go.
After my head showers only
it will die.
He knows ?, what I think?
Total should be in Oneido.
For the family? I'll be.
It has? like M & M'S? We have them.
We do not j ?. No, thank you.
It has? like crackers? We have them.
Do ara? Ide? No, thank you.
Tomorrow you can buy anything,
Today I'm not going anywhere.
What do you want to? No ?, boy?
? I read. It's very clever.
In which class go ??
In the? Fourth, fifth? ? It's complicated.
It's very clever. ? It is.
Why not lust? Eta jackets and remain?
? The ice is. Why not Burn?
Bo? these salaries amounted to a bill?
? Summer is the will? Is available.
Here are the? Four degrees.
How long are you staying? ? Are you serious?
? Ele in? I la. ? Calm down.
In the morning I visited the? Father,
then go on the bus. You can?
Stay as long as you begin ?,
I do not care. Not only heating TURN ON.
Summer is.
Jesus, Eleanor, exhausting you.
? I visited about? Eta, then we leave.
It has? like meat? Truco, boy?
In the freezer I have. No, thank you.
My sister is a real smudge.
? A lot of things have.
Here we can not sleep.
OK will.
Would you be better at?
Would you, but you can not afford to go ??.
? And would you be better?
We'll borrow your car.
? Where are you going? ? The hotel.
For God's sake, Eleanor. ? I will come back
after the visit. ? At what time?
Where are you going? ? The clock is 21 h.
Will? vehicles around the city with children?
I do not know whether the fuel.
In which hotel? ? Then? I will contract.
The room was in disarray.
There, we can not sleep.
If I knew that coming?
and leads? dense, would put away.
We containers? car or not?
I do not know whether the fuel.
I'll come back in the morning.
Iota.
The pool they have.
Closed for renovation. ? Code.
Dale mom's brother?
O? Fathers. Wedding contract are,
when they are old? a detached contract.
They were friends in the middle? School.
My on? E is? El in the military,
he fought in the Gulf War.
Dale was beside her.
O? E is back in ruins
really started causing ati? strange things.
Separate the two,
Dale it was moved.
I'm tired. Go to sleep.
When I close the? I? Utim,
as it? s been on the bus.
Why are you from? La?
Your all societies? Ina here.
You just answered.
I wanted to "Juilliard".
?? To study the game?
Yes. God, no. Music.
The music? ? Kornet play.
What? ? Kornet. Less? The trumpet.
I know what the cone.
Musician you? Yeah.
Why did not you say earlier?
? I did not tell you.
How long game ??
? From the 4th grade.
On the test
I heard to perfection? ala tone,
so they gave me
Cornet in free? no use.
Free? To use?
So look for? Started playing cornet?
I wanted to trumpet. Because
they had, they gave me a cornet.
I agreed,
because it was a la? s play and wear.
Luck he had. Yeah.
Even the middle? School, I played
in the band. U? Rests here.
They chose me to the team,
in which we were only the most? i.
We played in the discovery of new
war memorial in Syracuzi.
What a great thing.
? Hillary Clinton cut the ribbon.
I played solo.
What was the "Juilliardom"?
I passed the entrance exam.
We are not able to give full? Scholarships.
I did not have to? Olnino.
? Despair.
Neither does. I'm not convinced? Ana,
that I really? saw Atlant there.
What then?
I work as a waitress.
I played on the subway. ? No.
Yes.
I played the Beatles
and well deserve? contract.
So I realized
Dennis. ? In the subway?
He stared at me and really started to come
on the platform. Trains passing vehicles,
and he just sat
on the bench. ? They gave the money?
It Is.
Then I really started brings? Ati coffee.
One time I went
"Skittles". Lovely it was.
In the end, I have questions? Ala,
or I will be welcomed. ? What did he say?
To me no? E wrong.
Yes it is? E? the sound of my trumpet.
What did she do?
I said: "This is not the trumpet,
bu? ko, but cornet. "? But he?
I do not remember. He took me
in Korean? ar restaurant.
Kulsko was.
For? Ela we dru? Go.
? As a boy and a girl? ? Not immediately.
He had a band.
He invited me to play with them.
Guitar game. ? There? Know ?.
He threw it through the window.
I do not think he knows? a.
Emotional, I assume.
Where is it? Cornet? ? I do not know him ?.
Why not? ? Long story.
Cash this? Ave.
You sold it? Yeah.
Yours was. "Oldsov".
O If I bought it,
when I graduated from high school.
It was a great surprise.
I did not know it was there.
Some time have not seen him.
After granting me
the? I waited in the parking lot ?? u.
In his hand is a Ph.D.? Al trunks Profit
with a large red bow on.
You can no ?.
How is the title of the work,
which he wrote for the recital?
"Melody of warmth."
? Marvelously.
? I wrote a part for cornet.
Hi, Shelly.
?? Hi, Eleanor. ? This is Reggie.
You painted your hair.
Apparently they were sino? I in the pension.
Sorry about the mess.
It could be a little trashed.
? That? Where,? E work? 40 hours a week.
Why work? there?
Many other pubs is.
Ve? What?
Not you? E is this where I work.
We will be? you pay? ala
Insurance for car and ra? une?
Come on.
Because it seemed to me. Super.
Before the game ?, friends
to make more? a of us.
Where are they slept? And yeah not the 'Days
Inn. "? Cigarette against children.
Where's Dale? ? Sleep.
It has? like flakes? e? I got them.
It's okay. Here are the key i.
I'll call a cab.
Where to now?
? At the bus station.
Did you see the? Father?
You are not so in the? La? ? I am.
And you? Have you seen these?
Has anyone from? El to visit?
You? It is. ? I? On you,
since you in? la. ? What is it?
Taxi, please. Street Penwick 59th
To the bus station. Thank you.
What? En noise is this?
? The appliances is Dale. ? I know.
They say they are not advertised? A ?.
He knows ?, how many covers veteran
pension? Malo. Therefore kli? Show.
I do not understand,
Why is this so? when you sit next to him.
Your brother. Sam was.
When he deteriorated? Alo,
I have not seen up close. No pametuj.
After? Akala we at the corner.
? Return, Eleanor. ? Go to hell!
Calm down.
? I do not I know? returned.
Return. Eleanor? Eleanor?
? Al me, no? others do not.
? Okay, thank you.
Good they are.
Are you really will not? He knows? back there?
? Where? ? Home.
You said that he knows?
not? returned. ? Who knows.
Probably someday visit
brother. If it will ever come back.
And I'm worried for my sister, although
I would sometimes prefer to choke.
It could be the? La
to you in New York. Yeah.
I think I? La
to the west. ? The West?
My friend 'lives in Idaho.
On skis? I ?? u work. Good deserve? I.
Always he says,
so that we can? la work.
With cold vein. ? Nice. Videla
I have photos. No permanent cold.
Bo? to do so? ? I think.
Pa cone? ? What about him?
One day I will play again.
Mora ?. ? Read the book.
I have read it.
"The fruits of wrath" happy story for you.
It has? gift and obliged
you nurture.
O? Em talk ??
Perhaps playing Worst in the world.
I would not say. Otherwise, this would not be
They take the most? e.
I would not dare to "Juilliard".
The evil? And scaffolding? S your world
Art. ? You said it was dead.
And will, if great artists cornet
abandon and move to Idaho.
Promise you will? play again.
Promise you will? back to music.
I will, if the will? you. ? Agreed.
I dozed off.
? Deep breathing ?, when asleep ?.
I had a dream.
We were on the lake,
where I walked like a girl.
Dennis was there.
? You loved him?
I guess I have.
At least I think so.
He loved you?
He said he loves me,
but who knows?
First, it was nice, then
He became bad to me and lied.
You never know ?.
Think ?, that will be? Ever
wedding contract and have children?
Many asks? INCLUDES ?.
? Excuse me. I'm curious.
I think not.
I think I did not meant to be.
I'm not? E seen,
in order to succeed. ? I do not agree.
Someone sentimental.
? Successfully, if belong to each other.
Then leave.
These? Ava is,
that two such find.
Think ?, it will be? If ever seen?
? No.
If someone is up to you
does not behave as you deserve? i ?,
You do not deserve? and that this has.
Thus spoke my on? E.
I? What?
Will I? E seen? ? Here I am.
? When? of? la. Leaving ?, right?
Will I? E ever seen?
If the? ? I wanted.
We may correspond.
Something tells me that? Ez one
year will not? I remembered my name.
Not really.
Spra? Matches,
or will someone loved me.
Mo? Of which are quite good.
How many years has it? ? 12th
Super is the? E? I will.
Hi, Reg. Meet Corrino.
? Hi, Reggie.
Pleased to meet you. Beautiful home has ?.
Thank you. It was built by
Captain Francis Fowke l. 1898th
Designed by
It is also a natural history museum.
Very interesting. ? Neither does.
Many buildings are built.
Help me to show hi? O.
No thanks. The room I
grouch read this biography of Marx.
I was happy. ? Even me.
Good morning. Mo? The latest pra? A
from the French too? e. As you in? E ?.
Unbelievable.
I hope you la? On.
I prepared a vegetable frittata
and the palace effects without flour. Come on down.
Would you? E coffee?
No, thank you. Excellent on it.
Esa returns tomorrow at eight.
Corrina those of today
prepare supper. And lunch.
I can feed.
Do not forget your vitamins.
Why should? go?
It is Corrina.
Things stack of trunks ka.
Would you? La walk?
You should go.
This is for you. What's this?
Penne with candle im huband crunchy sprouts . For on the way .
Thanks, Reg .
So ? Yeah .
Corrina is very friendly .
Yeah , it seems great.
She says she likes to play ? Ah . ? Cool .
Your mother returned 27 call
It will be on learning ? er . Esa returns tomorrow morning .
I know . Do not worry .
So straight in Idaho ?
? I am not convinced ? Ana .
I think I need homes
and put in order .
Are you collect .
Sometimes the best.
Are you collect , think about it.
Nice to meet you .
? You, too .
It's only a few months ,
but as you would know this ?
? utim that I should
say a lot of things .
But suddenly I can not.
I could not stay forever.
Only for slow it should be.
It's okay .
Good on you.
MELODY TOPLINE
MEDIATRANSLATIONS