1
00:00:25,340 --> 00:00:30,300
THE WORLD UNSEEN

2
00:01:44,510 --> 00:01:50,700
Cape Town,South Africa,1952

3
00:01:59,580 --> 00:02:01,380
Bastards!

4
00:02:01,730 --> 00:02:02,930
Good day,Amina.

5
00:02:03,310 --> 00:02:04,780
Sergeant.

6
00:02:09,780 --> 00:02:10,870
Good day,Jacob.

7
00:02:10,870 --> 00:02:12,340
Sergeant Stewart.

8
00:02:12,550 --> 00:02:15,050
So,she finally got the place opened?

9
00:02:15,450 --> 00:02:16,910
Nice business to have.

10
00:02:17,410 --> 00:02:18,970
I imagine it is.

11
00:02:27,560 --> 00:02:30,130
These new laws are making life bloody hard for the police.

12
00:02:30,130 --> 00:02:32,930
They're not making it a picnic for the rest of us either.

13
00:02:33,650 --> 00:02:35,910
My colleague's waiting in the car.

14
00:02:36,260 --> 00:02:39,160
He has a problem with this sort of thing.

15
00:02:39,410 --> 00:02:42,820
You know it's an offence for blacks to eat in the same place as whites.

16
00:02:43,550 --> 00:02:44,960
There are no whites here.

17
00:02:44,960 --> 00:02:46,860
Present company excluded.

18
00:02:47,990 --> 00:02:49,940
As non-blacks then.

19
00:02:49,940 --> 00:02:51,830
This is an Indian area.

20
00:02:52,410 --> 00:02:55,120
Maybe coloureds,but no blacks.

21
00:02:57,430 --> 00:02:58,410
Passports.

22
00:02:58,410 --> 00:03:00,080
You know they have passes.

23
00:03:00,080 --> 00:03:02,150
I want to see them. Now!

24
00:03:07,530 --> 00:03:09,490
This is only a travel permit.

25
00:03:10,060 --> 00:03:11,350
Yes,sir.

26
00:03:11,350 --> 00:03:12,470
Where's your pass?

27
00:03:12,470 --> 00:03:13,650
But I don't have a pass,sir.

28
00:03:13,650 --> 00:03:15,360
I'm coloured,not black.

29
00:03:15,780 --> 00:03:17,420
Yeah,you look like a Kaffir to me.

30
00:03:17,420 --> 00:03:19,400
Her father was Dutch,

31
00:03:19,770 --> 00:03:20,970
like mine.

32
00:03:20,970 --> 00:03:23,270
You understand,Jacob,it's going to be difficult...

33
00:03:24,930 --> 00:03:27,040
Stewart,what are you talking to these people for?

34
00:03:29,470 --> 00:03:31,020
Calm down.

35
00:03:31,020 --> 00:03:34,610
You keep serving blacks and we'll kill the lot of them.

36
00:03:43,520 --> 00:03:46,430
Ma'am,it would be safer for you to leave now.

37
00:03:46,430 --> 00:03:48,020
You don't have to pay for the...

38
00:03:48,020 --> 00:03:50,220
I can finish my coffee,mister ...?

39
00:03:50,220 --> 00:03:51,270
Williams.

40
00:03:52,050 --> 00:03:53,140
Jacob Williams.

41
00:03:53,140 --> 00:03:54,510
I'm Madeline Smith.

42
00:03:54,900 --> 00:03:56,360
You run the post office.

43
00:03:56,360 --> 00:03:59,280
Well,you come in it. 10 a.m. every Tuesday and Friday.

44
00:04:00,820 --> 00:04:02,730
You're Amina's business partner, aren't you?

45
00:04:04,500 --> 00:04:07,430
Ah,well,no, I just work for Amina.

46
00:04:07,430 --> 00:04:09,850
Oh,I'm sorry. I forgot.

47
00:04:09,850 --> 00:04:13,090
Partnership would be illegal, wouldn't it?

48
00:04:17,050 --> 00:04:20,040
Thank you,for shielding me from the police.

49
00:04:27,100 --> 00:04:29,650
Would you excuse me?

50
00:04:36,610 --> 00:04:37,920
What is it?

51
00:04:39,050 --> 00:04:40,410
My grandmother.

52
00:04:42,020 --> 00:04:44,220
We'll get a new glass, a new frame.

53
00:04:44,720 --> 00:04:46,150
Are you OK?

54
00:04:47,270 --> 00:04:48,640
And you?

55
00:04:48,640 --> 00:04:51,340
I'm not so old that I can't dive for cover.

56
00:04:52,050 --> 00:04:54,140
Not to mention flirt with the customers.

57
00:05:15,000 --> 00:05:16,400
Milk...

58
00:05:23,010 --> 00:05:25,270
<i>Come in here and get ready for school,both of you!</i>

59
00:05:25,680 --> 00:05:27,590
Thank God we are moving out in a couple of months...

60
00:05:29,100 --> 00:05:30,690
before the next one comes.

61
00:05:31,610 --> 00:05:33,240
Say goodbye to papa.

62
00:05:37,930 --> 00:05:39,520
OK,Sam,Yasmine,upstairs!

63
00:05:39,970 --> 00:05:42,140
Go! Brush your teeth,get your books!

64
00:05:44,710 --> 00:05:45,620
Off!

65
00:06:04,320 --> 00:06:05,640
He said yes.

66
00:06:05,640 --> 00:06:06,970
We can go.

67
00:06:06,970 --> 00:06:07,870
Where?

68
00:06:07,870 --> 00:06:08,840
Out for lunch!

69
00:06:08,840 --> 00:06:10,440
To the "Location Caf?.

70
00:06:11,120 --> 00:06:13,380
I can't believe our husbands are letting us out of here.

71
00:06:13,820 --> 00:06:15,240
Come on,Miriam. Get dressed!

72
00:06:32,360 --> 00:06:33,550
Good morning!

73
00:06:39,400 --> 00:06:41,400
I'm so sorry. Amina,I'm sorry.

74
00:06:41,400 --> 00:06:43,110
Thank you,Doris.

75
00:06:43,500 --> 00:06:44,570
Please,leave it.

76
00:06:48,000 --> 00:06:49,780
They have staff to do that.

77
00:06:57,940 --> 00:06:59,240
Good morning,ladies.

78
00:06:59,240 --> 00:07:00,650
- Good morning. - Good morning.

79
00:07:00,650 --> 00:07:04,220
Our special today is lamb bredie and I have some nice fresh "koeksisters".

80
00:07:04,520 --> 00:07:06,260
What are "koeksisters"?

81
00:07:06,590 --> 00:07:08,470
It's a South African delicacy.

82
00:07:08,770 --> 00:07:12,210
A fried doughnut with syrup and coconut.

83
00:07:12,210 --> 00:07:13,900
Here,try one!

84
00:07:13,900 --> 00:07:15,500
See if you like it.

85
00:07:24,090 --> 00:07:25,730
It's delicious.

86
00:07:25,730 --> 00:07:30,650
Good. I'll send some over and I promise I'll try not to drop them this time.

87
00:07:34,310 --> 00:07:35,970
She thinks a lot of herself.

88
00:07:36,500 --> 00:07:37,900
Maybe she should.

89
00:07:37,900 --> 00:07:40,530
She owns a business and she's one of us.

90
00:07:40,850 --> 00:07:42,130
No,she's not.

91
00:07:42,470 --> 00:07:44,840
Where do you see any of our girls looking like that?

92
00:07:44,840 --> 00:07:45,670
Like what?

93
00:07:45,670 --> 00:07:48,050
Are you blind?!

94
00:07:48,050 --> 00:07:49,670
Like a man.

95
00:07:52,220 --> 00:07:54,290
Maybe it's easier to work in trousers.

96
00:08:08,130 --> 00:08:09,670
Daddy,is it far?

97
00:08:10,040 --> 00:08:12,690
I told you,Delhof's in the country. You'll like it there.

98
00:08:13,950 --> 00:08:16,090
Will we have a house there like our old one?

99
00:08:16,310 --> 00:08:18,760
We'll get a much bigger & better than the old one.

100
00:08:18,760 --> 00:08:20,040
With a big shop underneath.

101
00:08:20,040 --> 00:08:21,640
Who'll work in it?

102
00:08:21,640 --> 00:08:25,230
I will. And your mother. And we'll have a boy to help us.

103
00:08:25,230 --> 00:08:27,760
And we'll have a night watchman to guard the place at night.

104
00:08:45,310 --> 00:08:47,130
Shall we leave?

105
00:09:55,450 --> 00:09:58,230
We'll need to work hard, that's all.

106
00:11:12,600 --> 00:11:15,160
She would've been proud of you.

107
00:11:32,050 --> 00:11:33,590
Hello,Bhai.

108
00:11:34,360 --> 00:11:36,960
Mrs Benjamin is making some tea.

109
00:11:37,490 --> 00:11:39,650
She says you should go and help her.

110
00:11:41,510 --> 00:11:43,960
How hard is it to make tea?

111
00:11:49,010 --> 00:11:51,720
Here. It will give you some energy.

112
00:11:53,610 --> 00:11:54,880
Are you OK?

113
00:11:55,130 --> 00:11:56,530
Shall I call her?

114
00:11:57,610 --> 00:11:58,360
No.

115
00:12:01,060 --> 00:12:03,120
No,I'm OK.

116
00:12:04,200 --> 00:12:05,420
Going already?

117
00:12:05,420 --> 00:12:07,110
Yes,I need to go to the shop.

118
00:12:07,110 --> 00:12:09,250
Don't worry about it. Your sister-in-law's there.

119
00:12:11,180 --> 00:12:14,530
Here,love. You have a nice cup of tea.

120
00:12:14,530 --> 00:12:16,100
Thank you,Mrs Benjamin.

121
00:12:16,100 --> 00:12:18,520
He's not one for a chat, is he?

122
00:12:19,780 --> 00:12:22,580
No,he's not.

123
00:12:29,460 --> 00:12:30,870
There's nobody here.

124
00:12:33,640 --> 00:12:35,550
I don't know who you think is going to come flooding in

125
00:12:35,550 --> 00:12:39,230
to buy groceries at this time of day. Or any time.

126
00:12:42,060 --> 00:12:43,480
Where's the boy?

127
00:12:43,480 --> 00:12:44,420
Robert?

128
00:12:46,100 --> 00:12:48,170
He's making deliveries. He'll be back.

129
00:12:48,170 --> 00:12:49,450
Later?

130
00:12:50,230 --> 00:12:51,600
What are you doing?

131
00:12:51,990 --> 00:12:54,390
Has it been so long that you don't even remember?

132
00:12:56,270 --> 00:12:59,170
I suppose she doesn't like you to touch her when she's pregnant.

133
00:13:18,370 --> 00:13:20,860
You come to Cape Town once a week...

134
00:13:21,680 --> 00:13:23,040
Come and see me.

135
00:13:34,890 --> 00:13:36,290
Sit down.

136
00:13:47,730 --> 00:13:49,290
So what do you do after school?

137
00:13:49,550 --> 00:13:50,770
Homework.

138
00:13:50,770 --> 00:13:52,640
Good... Good.

139
00:13:56,380 --> 00:13:57,600
Do it then.

140
00:13:58,110 --> 00:13:59,630
I don't have any homework.

141
00:13:59,630 --> 00:14:00,450
Why not?

142
00:14:00,450 --> 00:14:01,730
She's only five.

143
00:14:01,730 --> 00:14:04,850
She doesn't get homework until big school.

144
00:14:08,230 --> 00:14:09,740
Hello,mister Husband.

145
00:14:09,740 --> 00:14:11,960
Or should I say: mister Father?

146
00:14:11,960 --> 00:14:12,960
Is it a boy?

147
00:14:12,960 --> 00:14:14,010
What a question!

148
00:14:15,060 --> 00:14:18,250
You have a beautiful baby girl.

149
00:14:31,120 --> 00:14:32,380
My son!

150
00:14:33,010 --> 00:14:35,100
I have traveled so long to see you.

151
00:14:49,090 --> 00:14:50,740
All these Africans!

152
00:14:50,740 --> 00:14:52,720
That's the problem with this country:

153
00:14:54,150 --> 00:14:55,860
too many black people.

154
00:14:56,070 --> 00:15:00,020
You should come home my son, it is a better life.

155
00:15:00,720 --> 00:15:02,420
How will Amina find a good husband here?

156
00:15:02,500 --> 00:15:05,500
There are plenty of families when she's ready.

157
00:15:05,630 --> 00:15:08,020
Of course she's ready! Where is she anyway?

158
00:15:08,020 --> 00:15:09,350
She's work--

159
00:15:10,480 --> 00:15:11,510
She couldn't come.

160
00:15:11,790 --> 00:15:12,750
Working?

161
00:15:12,960 --> 00:15:14,490
Did you say she's working?

162
00:15:14,710 --> 00:15:15,870
Where is she working?

163
00:15:16,920 --> 00:15:18,420
Cape Town.

164
00:15:20,490 --> 00:15:23,930
The girl needs to be brought back to a decent way of living.

165
00:15:24,200 --> 00:15:26,870
Why is she working? What is she doing?

166
00:15:28,990 --> 00:15:31,800
She must mix more. I know a family.

167
00:15:31,800 --> 00:15:34,260
The Alis. Do you know them?

168
00:15:34,260 --> 00:15:37,530
- Yes. - Invite them for dinner,on Sunday.

169
00:15:38,250 --> 00:15:40,590
Your son never lets us invite anyone.

170
00:15:45,710 --> 00:15:47,310
Amina will never come.

171
00:15:47,310 --> 00:15:50,500
It is Amina's duty to be where we tell her.

172
00:15:50,500 --> 00:15:52,360
She will come.

173
00:15:58,520 --> 00:16:01,930
Amina,you're late. They're here already. Hurry up inside.

174
00:16:01,930 --> 00:16:02,950
Who's here?

175
00:16:03,560 --> 00:16:04,500
Where are you going?

176
00:16:05,060 --> 00:16:05,700
Inside?

177
00:16:05,700 --> 00:16:06,740
Like this?

178
00:16:07,100 --> 00:16:10,330
Like this. Mum,this is who I am.

179
00:16:10,330 --> 00:16:11,870
What else do you want me to wear?

180
00:16:31,240 --> 00:16:32,960
I'll help you serve the food.

181
00:16:34,730 --> 00:16:37,720
I don't see why people say that our girls are too modern.

182
00:16:38,110 --> 00:16:41,390
They may want to go out for a while and find out things for themselves.

183
00:16:41,760 --> 00:16:46,950
But I think our girls always find it best to stay at home in the end.

184
00:16:46,950 --> 00:16:48,530
Doesn't Amina work anymore then?

185
00:16:48,530 --> 00:16:50,470
Only now and then.

186
00:16:50,740 --> 00:16:53,030
- But what about the caf-- - Why isn't anybody eating?

187
00:16:53,410 --> 00:16:57,250
Things have been so busy at the garage lately.

188
00:16:57,520 --> 00:17:00,120
I don't have time to stop for one minute.

189
00:17:00,870 --> 00:17:02,400
Sometimes I wish Amina was helping me again.

190
00:17:03,900 --> 00:17:07,260
And how many children would you like,Amina?

191
00:17:07,480 --> 00:17:12,440
Oh,I don't know... I suppose two or three would be nice.

192
00:17:12,700 --> 00:17:13,600
Do you want only boys?

193
00:17:13,740 --> 00:17:15,850
What would make you think I'd want boys at all?

194
00:17:16,050 --> 00:17:17,850
What a rubbish! Everybody wants a boy.

195
00:17:18,070 --> 00:17:19,560
Everybody!

196
00:17:19,560 --> 00:17:21,090
Well,I'm not everybody.

197
00:17:21,090 --> 00:17:22,960
And I wouldn't care if I had a boy or a girl

198
00:17:22,960 --> 00:17:25,010
as long as the child was healthy and happy.

199
00:17:25,220 --> 00:17:27,360
Nothing else really matters,does it?

200
00:17:27,960 --> 00:17:29,020
I think she's right.

201
00:17:29,610 --> 00:17:31,740
I think it's time for desert.

202
00:17:42,480 --> 00:17:44,250
We're going to Cape Town on the weekend.

203
00:17:44,970 --> 00:17:46,220
All of us?

204
00:17:48,430 --> 00:17:49,970
Do you remember when this came?

205
00:17:50,770 --> 00:17:52,050
Two weeks ago.

206
00:17:52,050 --> 00:17:54,390
It's from my sister,Rehmat.

207
00:17:54,390 --> 00:17:56,400
The one in Paris?

208
00:17:58,450 --> 00:17:59,630
Who told you that?

209
00:18:00,330 --> 00:18:01,770
Farah.

210
00:18:03,160 --> 00:18:06,200
She's coming with her husband.

211
00:18:08,150 --> 00:18:10,330
I'm going to go to sleep. You watch the shop.

212
00:19:00,420 --> 00:19:02,330
Farah,come and help me here!

213
00:19:02,330 --> 00:19:03,860
They'll be here any minute now.

214
00:19:03,860 --> 00:19:05,920
And you know how particular Omar is.

215
00:19:07,460 --> 00:19:09,450
Not as much as he likes to think.

216
00:19:15,710 --> 00:19:16,670
They're here!

217
00:19:16,670 --> 00:19:18,130
<i>I'm cooking!</i>

218
00:19:24,160 --> 00:19:26,450
Well,where is she?

219
00:19:26,450 --> 00:19:28,260
She's gone to the hotel to meet James.

220
00:19:28,530 --> 00:19:30,890
That's a stupid thing to do.

221
00:19:31,460 --> 00:19:32,980
Are they trying to get caught?

222
00:19:32,980 --> 00:19:34,510
They shouldn't even be here.

223
00:19:34,510 --> 00:19:36,980
- He's father's dying. - So what?!

224
00:19:36,980 --> 00:19:39,030
He'll be dead in a week and they'll be in jail.

225
00:19:39,030 --> 00:19:40,550
Do they think the police care?

226
00:19:40,550 --> 00:19:42,500
Which hotel is he staying at?

227
00:19:42,500 --> 00:19:43,700
At "The Royal".

228
00:19:43,700 --> 00:19:44,900
If you can believe it.

229
00:19:47,980 --> 00:19:49,870
I don't know who they think they are.

230
00:20:00,650 --> 00:20:02,650
And this is my other sister-in-law.

231
00:20:02,650 --> 00:20:03,970
This is Miriam.

232
00:20:03,970 --> 00:20:05,340
Hello.

233
00:20:07,880 --> 00:20:09,350
It took me a while to get used to it.

234
00:20:09,580 --> 00:20:11,950
Paris must be such a nightmare to get used to.

235
00:20:12,360 --> 00:20:14,820
I meant that it wasn't home,at first,

236
00:20:15,070 --> 00:20:16,660
for either of us.

237
00:20:16,660 --> 00:20:19,590
But then I realised that there were no gossiping neighbours,

238
00:20:19,590 --> 00:20:22,850
no list of rules, no need to stay home

239
00:20:23,070 --> 00:20:24,690
if I wanted to work.

240
00:20:24,870 --> 00:20:27,600
We were very sorry to hear about your father's illness.

241
00:20:27,600 --> 00:20:30,350
He gave us his blessing,finally.

242
00:20:30,950 --> 00:20:33,250
I suppose death can give you a different perspective

243
00:20:33,250 --> 00:20:34,790
on what's important.

244
00:20:34,790 --> 00:20:36,740
And now eating here with all of you and

245
00:20:36,740 --> 00:20:39,340
at the time that seemed impossible.

246
00:20:39,340 --> 00:20:40,880
Aren't you afraid?

247
00:20:40,880 --> 00:20:42,900
Of what could happen if you get caught?

248
00:20:42,900 --> 00:20:44,730
My husband is an idealist.

249
00:20:44,730 --> 00:20:46,690
We have no time for idealists these days.

250
00:20:46,690 --> 00:20:47,950
We have to be practical.

251
00:20:48,160 --> 00:20:50,150
Get what we can whenever we can.

252
00:20:50,640 --> 00:20:53,800
You know,my husband and you, you could be twins.

253
00:20:56,090 --> 00:20:58,340
We are twins.

254
00:21:02,150 --> 00:21:03,860
Why couldn't you tell me?

255
00:21:03,860 --> 00:21:07,310
Men never tell you anything.

256
00:21:14,640 --> 00:21:16,790
Miriam,why don't we get my brother

257
00:21:16,790 --> 00:21:18,770
to take us to the "Location Caf??

258
00:21:18,770 --> 00:21:20,760
I used to sneak out and go over there all the time

259
00:21:20,760 --> 00:21:23,140
on my school breaks.

260
00:21:24,110 --> 00:21:25,780
I should stay and help.

261
00:21:25,780 --> 00:21:28,370
Bhabhi,you go,I'll take care of the children.

262
00:21:29,660 --> 00:21:31,460
Farah can make us tea.

263
00:22:01,080 --> 00:22:02,830
Is that the Harjan girl?

264
00:22:03,530 --> 00:22:06,050
She's young and she owns this place,huh?

265
00:22:06,050 --> 00:22:07,070
With a partner.

266
00:22:07,070 --> 00:22:10,140
Imagine at her age to be the partner of a business

267
00:22:10,140 --> 00:22:11,880
and a good business too!

268
00:22:12,130 --> 00:22:13,990
Sunday is always her busiest day.

269
00:22:13,990 --> 00:22:15,850
I think she's done well for one of our girls.

270
00:22:15,850 --> 00:22:17,370
So do I.

271
00:22:17,820 --> 00:22:19,930
She's not totally one of our girls.

272
00:22:20,540 --> 00:22:23,180
Have you ever seen one of our girls with such...

273
00:22:23,180 --> 00:22:24,670
with such curly hair?

274
00:22:25,090 --> 00:22:26,920
Are you saying that she's part black?

275
00:22:28,560 --> 00:22:30,370
That's her grandmother,Begum.

276
00:22:30,370 --> 00:22:32,470
The child is Amina's mother.

277
00:22:32,470 --> 00:22:33,990
There was a big scandal.

278
00:22:33,990 --> 00:22:35,960
She messed around with the Africans.

279
00:22:38,200 --> 00:22:40,010
Should I pretend to be horrified?

280
00:22:40,010 --> 00:22:42,870
You know,plenty of white people, including some of his family,

281
00:22:42,870 --> 00:22:45,390
would sit there one day,just like you,all self-righteous,

282
00:22:45,390 --> 00:22:47,570
and accuse my children of being half-Indian.

283
00:22:47,780 --> 00:22:48,560
That's not the same thing.

284
00:22:48,560 --> 00:22:50,500
It's exactly the same thing.

285
00:22:51,280 --> 00:22:52,890
How can you live here,Omar?

286
00:22:52,890 --> 00:22:54,650
How can you bear to be in this place?

287
00:22:54,650 --> 00:22:56,480
South Africa is my home.

288
00:23:06,680 --> 00:23:10,100
You wanted ten pence worth... here you are...

289
00:23:27,860 --> 00:23:30,370
I'd like to serve someone over here,please.

290
00:23:37,910 --> 00:23:40,610
WHITES               NON-WHITES ONLY                          ONLY

291
00:23:50,690 --> 00:23:51,870
I love South Africa.

292
00:23:52,220 --> 00:23:53,530
What do you love about it?

293
00:23:53,530 --> 00:23:54,940
The freedom,the space.

294
00:23:54,940 --> 00:23:56,210
It's not like India.

295
00:23:56,210 --> 00:23:58,970
No,it's not. It's much worse.

296
00:23:58,970 --> 00:24:01,130
And God help anyone who tries to fight it.

297
00:24:01,130 --> 00:24:04,710
I fight it. And I think you probably did too.

298
00:24:05,010 --> 00:24:06,780
I fought so hard

299
00:24:07,170 --> 00:24:11,430
I had to leave with bruises on my face.

300
00:24:16,820 --> 00:24:19,350
Do you still like "koeksisters"?

301
00:24:19,630 --> 00:24:20,750
Yes,I do.

302
00:24:20,750 --> 00:24:23,370
And have you had any since that were better?

303
00:24:24,930 --> 00:24:25,900
Never.

304
00:24:25,900 --> 00:24:28,380
Good. I'll send some over. They're frying now.

305
00:24:28,380 --> 00:24:30,820
Amina,this gentleman here is looking for

306
00:24:30,820 --> 00:24:32,810
someone to help build him a garden.

307
00:24:32,810 --> 00:24:34,570
You want it or know someone who would?

308
00:24:34,570 --> 00:24:35,930
I want a vegetable garden,

309
00:24:35,930 --> 00:24:37,850
behind my house, back with a shop.

310
00:24:37,850 --> 00:24:39,150
I can do it.

311
00:24:39,150 --> 00:24:40,320
I want a big space.

312
00:24:40,320 --> 00:24:42,500
I need enough to sell not just to eat.

313
00:24:42,780 --> 00:24:44,910
If you want me to do it,I can.

314
00:24:45,300 --> 00:24:46,520
Can you come early?

315
00:24:46,520 --> 00:24:48,260
How about seven?

316
00:25:16,090 --> 00:25:17,190
Hello.

317
00:25:17,190 --> 00:25:18,940
That's the patch I'd like you to do.

318
00:25:18,940 --> 00:25:21,830
Mummy,why is she wearing trousers?

319
00:25:22,180 --> 00:25:23,900
Because she works outside.

320
00:25:26,720 --> 00:25:27,820
Don't forget their lunch.

321
00:25:27,820 --> 00:25:29,040
Thank you,Robert.

322
00:25:29,290 --> 00:25:32,570
Robert,give the young lady some chapatis and some tea when she starts working

323
00:25:32,570 --> 00:25:34,470
and there's fig jam in the fridge,yeah?

324
00:25:34,470 --> 00:25:35,970
Come.

325
00:25:43,010 --> 00:25:44,240
Good morning.

326
00:25:44,240 --> 00:25:45,690
Hello.

327
00:25:46,190 --> 00:25:47,690
Say hello to the lady.

328
00:25:47,690 --> 00:25:49,460
Hello,Ma'am.

329
00:25:51,280 --> 00:25:52,650
Come on!

330
00:25:56,010 --> 00:25:57,310
Bye!

331
00:26:35,930 --> 00:26:37,690
I... I brought you some food.

332
00:26:40,440 --> 00:26:41,750
Thank you.

333
00:26:43,000 --> 00:26:44,250
It smells delicious.

334
00:26:44,900 --> 00:26:46,580
I wish I could cook so well.

335
00:26:46,580 --> 00:26:48,120
But you work in a caf?

336
00:26:48,330 --> 00:26:50,010
All Jacob's recipes.

337
00:26:51,880 --> 00:26:53,390
Well,then you should learn.

338
00:26:53,390 --> 00:26:54,840
So my mother tells me.

339
00:26:54,840 --> 00:26:56,090
Your mother's right.

340
00:26:56,090 --> 00:26:58,160
What will you do when you get married?

341
00:26:58,640 --> 00:26:59,620
I don't know,I suppose I'll have to

342
00:26:59,620 --> 00:27:02,620
find someone who can cook.

343
00:27:05,990 --> 00:27:07,770
Have you eaten?

344
00:27:08,330 --> 00:27:09,540
Why don't you join me?

345
00:27:10,120 --> 00:27:12,100
I have to mind the shop.

346
00:27:21,530 --> 00:27:23,480
I just want to know you better.

347
00:27:24,610 --> 00:27:27,720
I'm just a housewife and a mother.

348
00:27:27,720 --> 00:27:29,720
And doesn't a housewife have thoughts and feelings

349
00:27:29,720 --> 00:27:32,190
and wishes, just like everyone else?

350
00:27:35,970 --> 00:27:39,120
You were the first person to smile at me at the caf?..

351
00:27:39,980 --> 00:27:41,820
...in eight days.

352
00:27:44,940 --> 00:27:46,830
I count it!

353
00:28:27,840 --> 00:28:29,400
What's this?

354
00:28:29,940 --> 00:28:31,320
Poetry.

355
00:28:35,550 --> 00:28:36,880
I can't take it.

356
00:28:36,880 --> 00:28:38,110
Don't you like reading?

357
00:28:38,110 --> 00:28:39,720
I love reading.

358
00:28:40,920 --> 00:28:42,800
I mean I used to...

359
00:28:43,050 --> 00:28:44,660
I used to read a lot...

360
00:28:46,590 --> 00:28:49,060
Please,keep it then.

361
00:28:51,050 --> 00:28:52,870
Stay for dinner.

362
00:28:52,870 --> 00:28:54,450
I should get going.

363
00:28:55,630 --> 00:28:57,760
No,you can't drive at night.

364
00:28:57,760 --> 00:28:58,420
I'll be fine.

365
00:28:58,420 --> 00:29:00,620
No. Maybe in town but here...

366
00:29:00,620 --> 00:29:03,180
The roads are just tracks.

367
00:29:04,200 --> 00:29:05,600
Stay.

368
00:29:48,600 --> 00:29:51,960
If you're going to stay, you should come inside.

369
00:29:53,480 --> 00:29:55,480
Your husband's not back yet?

370
00:29:55,480 --> 00:29:57,250
He works late in Cape Town.

371
00:29:57,250 --> 00:29:59,490
Usually he stays at his sister-in-...

372
00:30:00,000 --> 00:30:02,240
brother's place.

373
00:30:05,630 --> 00:30:06,610
The daal was delicious.

374
00:30:06,610 --> 00:30:08,520
Do you want some more?

375
00:30:08,520 --> 00:30:10,630
No,I would like to clean up though.

376
00:30:11,030 --> 00:30:13,380
There's hot water in the bathroom. Come.

377
00:30:57,500 --> 00:30:59,340
What are you doing?

378
00:31:05,010 --> 00:31:06,260
I couldn't sleep.

379
00:31:06,870 --> 00:31:08,300
Me neither.

380
00:31:10,090 --> 00:31:11,570
Let me get you some tea.

381
00:31:12,180 --> 00:31:14,200
I'll make the tea, Miriam.

382
00:31:18,390 --> 00:31:21,420
Miriam is always getting the tea for everyone.

383
00:31:28,640 --> 00:31:30,370
Tell me...

384
00:31:30,690 --> 00:31:32,680
Has anyone ever looked after you?

385
00:31:40,720 --> 00:31:42,750
When did you come to South Africa?

386
00:31:44,140 --> 00:31:46,990
Seven years ago, after I got married.

387
00:31:46,990 --> 00:31:48,420
Me too!

388
00:31:49,510 --> 00:31:51,570
Our first evening off of a boat from India

389
00:31:51,570 --> 00:31:54,070
and we walk straight into the Indian congress protest.

390
00:31:54,070 --> 00:31:58,320
There were sticks and guns and policemen. I was...

391
00:31:59,040 --> 00:32:00,170
...terrified.

392
00:32:00,170 --> 00:32:01,370
I was there.

393
00:32:01,370 --> 00:32:03,320
Protesting The Ghetto Bill.

394
00:32:03,320 --> 00:32:06,420
I thought we could overthrow the government in two weeks.

395
00:32:10,670 --> 00:32:13,090
Is there anything that you don't do?

396
00:32:14,710 --> 00:32:17,820
I have to give people something to talk about.

397
00:32:18,050 --> 00:32:21,700
Do you ever think about getting married and having children instead?

398
00:32:21,990 --> 00:32:24,500
Yeah,it's that word "instead" I don't like.

399
00:32:24,500 --> 00:32:26,620
Why can't a woman do both if she wants to?

400
00:32:26,920 --> 00:32:28,140
It's not usual.

401
00:32:28,140 --> 00:32:31,980
No. But neither am I, and neither are you.

402
00:32:35,330 --> 00:32:37,750
Where did you learn to think like this?

403
00:32:39,410 --> 00:32:40,580
My grandmother...

404
00:32:40,580 --> 00:32:42,220
My mother's mother...

405
00:32:42,220 --> 00:32:43,880
The picture in the caf?

406
00:32:44,130 --> 00:32:47,100
She lived here once before she was sent back to India.

407
00:32:48,070 --> 00:32:50,920
You must have heard someone's version of the story.

408
00:32:51,150 --> 00:32:52,890
There's always gossip...

409
00:32:54,600 --> 00:32:58,690
Tell me the story. The real story, if you don't mind.

410
00:32:59,630 --> 00:33:01,560
I'd like to tell you.

411
00:33:02,600 --> 00:33:06,060
I think you'd understand why my grandmother was so important to me.

412
00:33:06,520 --> 00:33:08,010
What happened to her?

413
00:33:18,650 --> 00:33:20,630
She was 19,

414
00:33:20,920 --> 00:33:23,240
with one child already.

415
00:33:25,840 --> 00:33:30,860
And shame and dishonour of being rapped,she tried to hide it.

416
00:33:32,290 --> 00:33:34,730
But she became pregnant.

417
00:33:36,350 --> 00:33:40,710
As soon as the baby was born, my mother,

418
00:33:40,980 --> 00:33:43,700
they realised it wasn't her husband's.

419
00:33:44,240 --> 00:33:45,890
What did they do to her?

420
00:34:06,670 --> 00:34:08,690
They put her on a train to Durban,

421
00:34:09,310 --> 00:34:11,500
to get a boat to Bombay.

422
00:34:31,190 --> 00:34:35,160
Hold him out so I can kiss him. Please... Please...

423
00:34:35,160 --> 00:34:35,930
No!

424
00:34:35,930 --> 00:34:40,190
No! Stop! Stop the train! No!

425
00:34:40,700 --> 00:34:43,850
No! Stop! No!

426
00:34:53,390 --> 00:34:56,370
I can't imagine losing a child like that.

427
00:34:56,370 --> 00:34:58,320
It broke her.

428
00:34:59,260 --> 00:35:03,110
She didn't have one choice to make her whole life.

429
00:35:03,930 --> 00:35:05,590
And for as long as I can remember

430
00:35:05,930 --> 00:35:10,850
she always warned be about the dangers of being oppressed in a marriage.

431
00:35:11,130 --> 00:35:13,440
Is that why you haven't gotten married?

432
00:35:15,210 --> 00:35:17,470
That's not the only reason.

433
00:35:25,080 --> 00:35:26,840
Miriam?

434
00:35:27,630 --> 00:35:29,400
Yes?

435
00:35:31,930 --> 00:35:33,430
Nothing.

436
00:35:33,430 --> 00:35:35,800
You should go, the baby needs you.

437
00:35:59,380 --> 00:36:01,270
Sam? Yasmine!

438
00:36:01,880 --> 00:36:04,120
Auntie Amina was showing us the garden.

439
00:36:04,800 --> 00:36:06,330
Are you ready for school?

440
00:36:07,670 --> 00:36:08,970
Did you eat?

441
00:36:08,970 --> 00:36:11,710
Auntie Amina gave us some breakfast.

442
00:36:13,730 --> 00:36:14,790
Here we go.

443
00:36:14,790 --> 00:36:15,550
OK.

444
00:36:15,900 --> 00:36:19,070
I've never imagined I'd be so domesticated.

445
00:36:19,180 --> 00:36:21,200
I've never imagined anything else.

446
00:36:21,850 --> 00:36:24,220
OK,kids. You ready for school?

447
00:36:24,220 --> 00:36:25,700
Come on.

448
00:36:26,760 --> 00:36:28,300
Have a good day!

449
00:36:32,720 --> 00:36:34,450
Can I make you some breakfast?

450
00:36:34,820 --> 00:36:36,420
Perhaps later.

451
00:36:36,420 --> 00:36:37,990
I'm going to start work.

452
00:36:43,770 --> 00:36:48,600
I hope I didn't worry you with all my strange ideas and stories last night.

453
00:36:50,510 --> 00:36:53,020
No,you made me think and that's

454
00:36:53,600 --> 00:36:57,120
supposed to be a good thing, isn't it?

455
00:36:57,470 --> 00:36:59,270
That depends on who you ask.

456
00:37:04,060 --> 00:37:05,610
What are you doing?

457
00:37:08,260 --> 00:37:09,360
Reading.

458
00:37:09,360 --> 00:37:12,360
I can see that. Reading what?!

459
00:37:14,020 --> 00:37:15,600
Poetry.

460
00:37:16,590 --> 00:37:17,980
Poetry.

461
00:37:18,200 --> 00:37:19,920
At this time of night?!

462
00:37:21,940 --> 00:37:23,230
I'm tired.

463
00:37:24,570 --> 00:37:26,750
I was busy in Cape Town today.

464
00:37:26,750 --> 00:37:28,850
With her?

465
00:37:29,080 --> 00:37:30,770
What did you say?

466
00:37:32,450 --> 00:37:33,900
Nothing.

467
00:37:53,100 --> 00:37:55,060
<i>"Love bade me welcome,</i>

468
00:37:55,500 --> 00:37:57,380
<i>yet my soul drew back,</i>

469
00:37:57,380 --> 00:37:59,560
<i>Guilty of dust and sin.</i>

470
00:37:59,560 --> 00:38:01,490
<i>But quick-ey'd Love,</i>

471
00:38:01,490 --> 00:38:03,090
observing me grow slack

472
00:38:03,090 --> 00:38:05,490
From my first entrance in,

473
00:38:05,490 --> 00:38:08,850
Drew nearer to me,sweetly questioning

474
00:38:08,850 --> 00:38:10,980
If I lack'd anything.

475
00:38:10,980 --> 00:38:14,290
"A guest," I answer'd,"worthy to be here";

476
00:38:14,560 --> 00:38:17,610
Love said,"You shall be he."

477
00:38:19,300 --> 00:38:20,490
Afternoon.

478
00:38:20,490 --> 00:38:22,210
We need to ask you some questions.

479
00:38:22,210 --> 00:38:24,080
My husband is not here, he just left.

480
00:38:24,080 --> 00:38:26,040
Yeah,we must've just missed him.

481
00:38:26,300 --> 00:38:28,110
Robert,get these gentlemen a drink.

482
00:38:31,490 --> 00:38:32,940
It's a good shop you have here.

483
00:38:33,820 --> 00:38:34,680
Thank you.

484
00:38:36,260 --> 00:38:37,990
Is your sister-in-law here?

485
00:38:39,680 --> 00:38:42,340
My brother-in-law and his wife stay in town.

486
00:38:44,920 --> 00:38:47,440
We're looking for Rehmat Winston.

487
00:38:47,780 --> 00:38:49,980
And we know she's staying with you.

488
00:38:50,730 --> 00:38:51,820
They're not here.

489
00:38:53,310 --> 00:38:54,930
So you know where they are.

490
00:39:08,040 --> 00:39:09,870
Listen.

491
00:39:10,150 --> 00:39:13,830
You'll be in a pile of shit if you help them.

492
00:39:14,590 --> 00:39:16,490
What have they done?

493
00:39:17,390 --> 00:39:21,050
Have you heard of the Prohibition of Mixed Marriages Act of 1949?

494
00:39:21,300 --> 00:39:22,980
It's there for a reason.

495
00:39:24,510 --> 00:39:27,860
To stop this depravity.

496
00:39:28,260 --> 00:39:31,950
It's against nature what these people are doing.

497
00:39:33,410 --> 00:39:34,750
Home from school.

498
00:39:34,750 --> 00:39:35,520
No,you can't.

499
00:39:35,520 --> 00:39:36,300
Yes,we can.

500
00:39:36,300 --> 00:39:38,640
They may be witholding valuable information.

501
00:39:38,640 --> 00:39:40,800
No! No! Please!

502
00:39:40,800 --> 00:39:42,300
Have you ever been to a police station,young lady?

503
00:39:42,300 --> 00:39:44,260
Where are we going?

504
00:39:44,260 --> 00:39:45,410
Stop!

505
00:39:47,890 --> 00:39:49,510
We'll bring them back later.

506
00:39:49,510 --> 00:39:51,440
Or tomorrow,whenever we get time.

507
00:39:52,060 --> 00:39:53,600
No,I'll tell you where they are!

508
00:39:53,600 --> 00:39:54,860
Too late!

509
00:39:57,940 --> 00:40:00,690
So? Where are they?

510
00:40:01,250 --> 00:40:02,690
Where are they?

511
00:40:03,630 --> 00:40:05,040
In Cape Town.

512
00:40:07,210 --> 00:40:09,370
At my brother-in-law's.

513
00:40:10,310 --> 00:40:12,080
You know,if you're lying,

514
00:40:12,080 --> 00:40:15,330
I'll beat you,and your children, and your baby!

515
00:40:53,730 --> 00:40:56,290
I need help. The police are after us.

516
00:40:56,630 --> 00:40:57,490
We can't.

517
00:40:57,490 --> 00:40:58,950
Amina,you have to.

518
00:40:58,950 --> 00:41:00,640
We can't help you.

519
00:41:00,910 --> 00:41:01,790
I'm sorry.

520
00:41:04,060 --> 00:41:05,560
Please,please,sit.

521
00:41:05,820 --> 00:41:09,050
I understand. It's just... I don't know what to do.

522
00:41:09,480 --> 00:41:10,870
If we helped you in front of the customers,

523
00:41:10,870 --> 00:41:13,000
someone would break when the police start threatening.

524
00:41:14,020 --> 00:41:15,770
Are you sure?

525
00:41:17,910 --> 00:41:20,130
Thank you for this, I...

526
00:41:28,840 --> 00:41:31,000
You were supposed to tell us.

527
00:41:34,980 --> 00:41:36,850
In front of my husband?!

528
00:41:37,290 --> 00:41:42,020
Was I supposed to tell it while she could hear me,hiding upstairs?

529
00:41:42,020 --> 00:41:45,140
What kind of state police don't even search the house?

530
00:41:49,630 --> 00:41:52,150
Where are they now?

531
00:41:54,010 --> 00:41:55,600
Some nice clothes...

532
00:41:55,600 --> 00:41:57,390
French labels.

533
00:41:58,210 --> 00:41:59,990
We'll find them.

534
00:41:59,990 --> 00:42:03,560
You'll be the next, for helping them.

535
00:42:07,250 --> 00:42:09,300
I'm not stupid.

536
00:42:11,360 --> 00:42:14,310
But there is someone around here who is.

537
00:42:16,000 --> 00:42:19,390
And it won't be the first time she's in trouble with the two of you.

538
00:42:44,790 --> 00:42:47,000
Stop that bloody noise!

539
00:42:55,090 --> 00:42:56,130
Jacob.

540
00:42:56,130 --> 00:42:57,210
Sergeant?

541
00:42:57,210 --> 00:43:00,090
We're looking for an Indian woman.

542
00:43:00,610 --> 00:43:02,310
Indians is all we get in here.

543
00:43:02,310 --> 00:43:04,420
But you're welcome to have a look around.

544
00:43:05,170 --> 00:43:06,370
Where's Amina?

545
00:43:06,370 --> 00:43:07,320
She's having a nap.

546
00:43:07,320 --> 00:43:08,890
She'll be taking over from me shortly.

547
00:43:08,890 --> 00:43:11,080
I'm not as young as I used to be.

548
00:43:24,570 --> 00:43:25,660
I know she's here.

549
00:43:26,300 --> 00:43:27,090
Who?

550
00:43:35,150 --> 00:43:36,600
Open this up!

551
00:43:37,970 --> 00:43:38,730
Go,go,go!

552
00:43:38,730 --> 00:43:40,160
Open it!

553
00:43:46,520 --> 00:43:47,580
What's all that?

554
00:43:47,580 --> 00:43:49,400
Stock for the caf?

555
00:43:50,770 --> 00:43:52,480
That's why I keep it locked.

556
00:43:52,750 --> 00:43:55,590
Those Kaffirs would steal anything.

557
00:43:58,370 --> 00:44:00,760
Tell me where she is!

558
00:44:02,070 --> 00:44:04,360
I really don't know who you're talking about.

559
00:44:04,710 --> 00:44:07,270
You and I both know that I've had some women in here,but this time even I...

560
00:44:08,570 --> 00:44:10,340
Stinkin' queer!

561
00:44:29,110 --> 00:44:31,040
Hey,yours is the only place in town

562
00:44:31,040 --> 00:44:33,320
where Kaffir workers eat alongside Indians.

563
00:44:33,320 --> 00:44:35,130
You get away with it.

564
00:44:35,130 --> 00:44:36,710
Yes.

565
00:44:36,710 --> 00:44:39,780
I could've closed you down anytime,couldn't I?

566
00:44:42,330 --> 00:44:43,560
Yes.

567
00:44:43,560 --> 00:44:44,310
So?

568
00:44:46,260 --> 00:44:47,960
Was she here?

569
00:44:47,960 --> 00:44:48,710
No.

570
00:44:49,930 --> 00:44:51,440
Where is she?

571
00:44:51,440 --> 00:44:54,090
I really don't know.

572
00:44:55,700 --> 00:44:57,420
I'm sorry.

573
00:45:05,050 --> 00:45:06,210
Who's that?

574
00:45:06,610 --> 00:45:08,700
If it's the police,then I'll deal with them this time.

575
00:45:11,920 --> 00:45:13,170
Someone's here.

576
00:45:13,380 --> 00:45:14,500
My goddamn truck.

577
00:45:14,500 --> 00:45:14,960
What happened?

578
00:45:14,960 --> 00:45:16,730
My lights have gone.

579
00:45:16,730 --> 00:45:18,690
Hit a bloody Kaffir walking in the yard,

580
00:45:18,690 --> 00:45:20,060
pulling right in my way.

581
00:45:20,280 --> 00:45:23,250
Thought it was just one side he caught, but both my lights have gone.

582
00:45:23,250 --> 00:45:24,640
We might have one of those.

583
00:45:24,640 --> 00:45:25,780
Miriam!

584
00:45:25,780 --> 00:45:26,930
Thanks.

585
00:45:33,840 --> 00:45:34,920
Ah,that's the right one.

586
00:45:34,920 --> 00:45:35,810
How is he?

587
00:45:38,210 --> 00:45:39,040
Who?

588
00:45:39,370 --> 00:45:41,140
The Kaffir. How is he?

589
00:45:41,140 --> 00:45:42,780
Dead,I hope.

590
00:45:48,930 --> 00:45:51,080
Just look at it. Both lights.

591
00:45:51,600 --> 00:45:52,520
That should fit.

592
00:45:52,520 --> 00:45:53,250
You reckon?

593
00:45:53,250 --> 00:45:54,490
Yes. Try it.

594
00:45:55,950 --> 00:45:57,850
Come on! Light it!

595
00:46:15,220 --> 00:46:15,810
Are you OK?

596
00:46:15,810 --> 00:46:17,120
I'm fine.

597
00:46:24,310 --> 00:46:25,640
Where are you?

598
00:46:27,490 --> 00:46:28,620
I can help.

599
00:46:32,290 --> 00:46:33,610
Let me help you.

600
00:46:36,990 --> 00:46:38,550
I don't need your help!

601
00:46:53,550 --> 00:46:55,220
I don't need your help.

602
00:47:25,890 --> 00:47:27,140
Where were you?

603
00:47:31,190 --> 00:47:33,140
I thought I left the washing out.

604
00:47:49,460 --> 00:47:51,620
Your place is here with me.

605
00:47:52,560 --> 00:47:54,580
Not with those Kaffirs.

606
00:48:34,210 --> 00:48:35,970
Oh! You found them!

607
00:48:36,820 --> 00:48:38,380
Books,madam. You forgot them?

608
00:48:38,380 --> 00:48:40,370
Yes,until somebody reminded me.

609
00:49:05,950 --> 00:49:08,540
Robert,take this. Take it to the post office.

610
00:49:26,460 --> 00:49:27,650
Here you are.

611
00:49:28,270 --> 00:49:29,060
Good morning,Jacob.

612
00:49:29,270 --> 00:49:30,520
Good morning,Madeline.

613
00:49:30,780 --> 00:49:31,890
Warm out today,isn't it?

614
00:49:31,890 --> 00:49:33,470
You can say that again.

615
00:49:34,130 --> 00:49:36,320
Hey,boy. Get me some water!

616
00:49:38,560 --> 00:49:40,590
Go on! You understand English,do you?

617
00:49:40,590 --> 00:49:41,810
There's a jug over there.

618
00:49:43,660 --> 00:49:46,390
Listen,I'm the employee here and

619
00:49:46,390 --> 00:49:49,970
I'll get you the water if you are incapable of getting it yourself.

620
00:49:52,960 --> 00:49:54,430
What's the matter with you,lady?

621
00:49:54,700 --> 00:49:56,310
That will be six pence for the stamps.

622
00:50:14,050 --> 00:50:16,450
All of us here are losing our dignity as human beings in this place,

623
00:50:16,450 --> 00:50:17,600
aren't we?

624
00:50:17,600 --> 00:50:19,890
Some of us more quickly than others.

625
00:50:19,890 --> 00:50:22,820
Oh,no. Don't you believe that for a second.

626
00:50:22,820 --> 00:50:25,130
It's men like him who lose the most.

627
00:50:26,420 --> 00:50:28,310
Perhaps...

628
00:50:30,080 --> 00:50:31,660
I've got a parcel here for you.

629
00:50:32,600 --> 00:50:34,560
Or rather for the young miss Harjan.

630
00:50:35,250 --> 00:50:37,190
Here. There's no other post.

631
00:50:40,850 --> 00:50:42,570
There's no return address.

632
00:50:42,570 --> 00:50:45,600
No. Perhaps it's from a secret paramour.

633
00:50:50,220 --> 00:50:53,370
I'd better get back.

634
00:50:54,090 --> 00:50:55,840
I'll see you soon.

635
00:50:56,890 --> 00:50:58,390
Jacob!

636
00:50:59,050 --> 00:51:00,890
Be sure that you do.

637
00:51:13,370 --> 00:51:15,260
This came for you today.

638
00:51:17,560 --> 00:51:18,690
Thank you.

639
00:51:19,990 --> 00:51:23,650
It's... It's not my mother's handwriting.

640
00:51:32,060 --> 00:51:36,070
<i><b>"All the wild summer was in her gaze"</b></i>

641
00:51:44,730 --> 00:51:46,670
She's not gonna work all the time!

642
00:51:46,670 --> 00:51:49,630
This is still so difficult, because he's too young.

643
00:51:52,020 --> 00:51:53,280
What are you doing?

644
00:51:53,280 --> 00:51:54,750
It's the Alis.

645
00:51:54,750 --> 00:51:57,140
They've come to give their reply.

646
00:51:58,500 --> 00:52:00,530
Even my mother must realise it's going to be no.

647
00:52:04,610 --> 00:52:06,410
Won't you have some tea?

648
00:52:06,410 --> 00:52:08,260
Send that girl to me at once!

649
00:52:09,050 --> 00:52:10,030
Who? Amina?

650
00:52:10,030 --> 00:52:10,990
Of course.

651
00:52:10,990 --> 00:52:13,360
She needs discipline now.

652
00:52:14,570 --> 00:52:16,330
Send me the doctor.

653
00:52:16,330 --> 00:52:17,740
I'm dying.

654
00:52:18,170 --> 00:52:19,710
She'll be fine.

655
00:52:20,660 --> 00:52:22,590
Ma',just...

656
00:52:25,700 --> 00:52:27,260
Just take her some tea.

657
00:52:27,500 --> 00:52:28,430
But she's dying.

658
00:52:28,430 --> 00:52:31,290
She's been claiming an imminent death for 30 years.

659
00:52:31,720 --> 00:52:34,720
Please,just... Take her some tea.

660
00:52:53,620 --> 00:52:55,070
Ma'!

661
00:52:55,490 --> 00:52:57,030
Dinner is ready!

662
00:53:03,410 --> 00:53:06,200
Ma',your tea must be ice cold.

663
00:53:10,310 --> 00:53:13,010
I don't have time to go driving around the countryside

664
00:53:13,010 --> 00:53:15,010
for some old woman we didn't even know.

665
00:53:16,100 --> 00:53:17,880
That family don't mix with any of us.

666
00:53:17,880 --> 00:53:20,290
Yet,when it suits them,they expect all of us to just come running.

667
00:53:20,290 --> 00:53:21,760
They don't expect it.

668
00:53:21,760 --> 00:53:23,670
I don't owe those people anything!

669
00:53:23,670 --> 00:53:25,020
Yes,you do.

670
00:53:25,020 --> 00:53:27,690
Amina Harjan saved your sister.

671
00:53:29,380 --> 00:53:31,230
After Farah betrayed her.

672
00:54:17,850 --> 00:54:19,890
Auntie,is Amina here?

673
00:54:19,890 --> 00:54:22,460
I'd like to offer my condolences.

674
00:54:23,890 --> 00:54:25,790
- She's in the next room. - OK.

675
00:54:26,830 --> 00:54:29,390
Please see if she will join us.

676
00:54:52,270 --> 00:54:54,030
I'm reading your book.

677
00:54:54,030 --> 00:54:56,380
I'd forgotten I even had them un-,until...

678
00:54:56,610 --> 00:54:58,190
I didn't know you knew my parents.

679
00:54:58,190 --> 00:55:00,980
I don't. We came to see you.

680
00:55:01,300 --> 00:55:02,690
The murderess?!

681
00:55:03,150 --> 00:55:05,060
Apparently my work and my trousers

682
00:55:05,370 --> 00:55:07,240
caused the heart attack.

683
00:55:12,170 --> 00:55:14,840
I can't tell whether you approve of my clothes or not.

684
00:55:20,950 --> 00:55:22,490
They're nice.

685
00:55:24,160 --> 00:55:26,400
It's a nice outfit.

686
00:55:27,550 --> 00:55:30,970
I mean that you look nice in it.

687
00:55:31,370 --> 00:55:33,520
So you prefer me in traditional clothes?

688
00:55:33,520 --> 00:55:35,300
No...

689
00:55:35,790 --> 00:55:37,780
You look very nice in this.

690
00:55:37,780 --> 00:55:40,120
But you don't look like youself.

691
00:55:41,210 --> 00:55:43,290
I don't feel like myself!

692
00:55:44,840 --> 00:55:47,350
But I have to please a person who,

693
00:55:47,770 --> 00:55:51,450
God rest her soul,is not even able to see me.

694
00:55:55,740 --> 00:55:58,400
It sounds silly when you put it like that.

695
00:55:58,400 --> 00:56:00,400
It is silly.

696
00:56:00,400 --> 00:56:02,630
But no one else seems to think so.

697
00:56:06,150 --> 00:56:08,310
Does it matter what people think?

698
00:56:09,870 --> 00:56:11,930
Doesn't it?

699
00:56:12,370 --> 00:56:14,200
Why did you get married?

700
00:56:14,850 --> 00:56:15,790
Did you fall in love and

701
00:56:15,790 --> 00:56:17,920
know you wanted to be with him

702
00:56:17,920 --> 00:56:20,060
for the rest of your life?

703
00:56:20,270 --> 00:56:21,020
No.

704
00:56:23,170 --> 00:56:25,420
He saw me a few times and...

705
00:56:26,540 --> 00:56:28,150
proposed and...

706
00:56:28,450 --> 00:56:30,100
my family accepted.

707
00:56:30,490 --> 00:56:32,290
And that's what you want to hear,isn't it?

708
00:56:32,520 --> 00:56:34,640
That it never occured to me to question it.

709
00:56:34,930 --> 00:56:36,900
It occurs to me to question it.

710
00:56:37,130 --> 00:56:39,250
I know.

711
00:56:44,330 --> 00:56:46,620
What happened to your face?

712
00:56:46,910 --> 00:56:48,490
Nothing.

713
00:56:55,370 --> 00:56:57,900
Your mother wants to see you downstairs.

714
00:56:57,900 --> 00:56:59,920
My husband wants to see you too.

715
00:56:59,920 --> 00:57:01,130
To thank you.

716
00:57:01,130 --> 00:57:02,160
For what?

717
00:57:02,160 --> 00:57:04,150
For Rehmat.

718
00:57:04,150 --> 00:57:06,060
Anyone would've done the same.

719
00:57:06,060 --> 00:57:07,500
I didn't.

720
00:57:08,210 --> 00:57:09,950
Did they hurt you?

721
00:57:11,050 --> 00:57:12,220
The police?

722
00:57:13,570 --> 00:57:15,320
They were taking my children away.

723
00:57:16,010 --> 00:57:17,990
Then you did the right thing.

724
00:57:20,650 --> 00:57:22,240
Come.

725
00:57:22,860 --> 00:57:25,200
I want to change back into my own clothes.

726
00:57:40,190 --> 00:57:42,420
Why should you take that risk?

727
00:57:42,920 --> 00:57:44,750
Because I hate apartheid.

728
00:57:46,570 --> 00:57:49,440
Because I hate aggressive policemen.

729
00:57:49,780 --> 00:57:52,120
I wish I could be more like you.

730
00:58:03,040 --> 00:58:07,300
Be careful what you wish for...

731
00:58:07,520 --> 00:58:08,600
...Miriam.

732
00:58:22,000 --> 00:58:23,220
Jacob?

733
00:58:23,690 --> 00:58:24,970
I have an idea.

734
00:58:25,780 --> 00:58:27,650
You haven't had a bad one yet.

735
00:58:27,650 --> 00:58:29,080
What is it?

736
00:58:30,140 --> 00:58:31,750
Indian food.

737
00:58:31,750 --> 00:58:35,440
All sorts of things: samosas,biryanis...

738
00:58:36,500 --> 00:58:37,370
OK...

739
00:58:38,130 --> 00:58:39,770
But you know our girls don't know

740
00:58:39,770 --> 00:58:42,250
the first thing about making a proper Indian curry.

741
00:58:43,200 --> 00:58:45,170
So who's gonna do the cooking?

742
00:58:45,720 --> 00:58:46,880
Don't worry.

743
00:58:47,210 --> 00:58:49,110
I've already thought of that.

744
00:59:19,210 --> 00:59:21,070
Where you just passing through?

745
00:59:22,440 --> 00:59:24,850
No offence to you... there down... but I...

746
00:59:25,160 --> 00:59:26,260
It's OK...

747
00:59:26,260 --> 00:59:28,890
...but I don't think anybody just passes through.

748
00:59:29,200 --> 00:59:30,730
I came to see you.

749
00:59:31,210 --> 00:59:33,830
Will you have some tea? A cold drink?

750
00:59:34,770 --> 00:59:36,380
I want to talk to you.

751
00:59:36,380 --> 00:59:38,020
About the caf?

752
00:59:38,500 --> 00:59:40,010
We're thinking about something new. Indian food.

753
00:59:40,010 --> 00:59:41,690
Maybe a few days a week.

754
00:59:41,690 --> 00:59:43,410
It's a good idea.

755
00:59:44,910 --> 00:59:46,830
I want you to cook for the caf?

756
00:59:46,830 --> 00:59:48,070
Me?

757
00:59:52,400 --> 00:59:54,250
You haven't even had my cooking.

758
00:59:54,250 --> 00:59:55,820
I ate here, remember?

759
00:59:55,820 --> 00:59:57,520
Potato curry and daal.

760
01:00:04,330 --> 01:00:05,910
Besides,I couldn't do it.

761
01:00:07,340 --> 01:00:08,590
Why not?

762
01:00:08,590 --> 01:00:10,850
Because I have to take care of the shop.

763
01:00:13,020 --> 01:00:14,690
We'd pay you well.

764
01:00:16,830 --> 01:00:18,070
My children.

765
01:00:18,070 --> 01:00:22,370
OK,then we'll make it one morning a week to start with.

766
01:00:26,030 --> 01:00:27,600
My husband wouldn't like it.

767
01:00:27,600 --> 01:00:31,010
I'm offering the job to you, not your husband.

768
01:00:32,900 --> 01:00:34,250
You surprise me.

769
01:00:36,040 --> 01:00:38,310
I thought you had a fearless streak.

770
01:00:40,990 --> 01:00:45,260
How would you know whether I have a fearless streak or not?

771
01:00:47,700 --> 01:00:49,580
Wasn't it you who went out in the middle of the night

772
01:00:49,580 --> 01:00:52,370
to help an African who was hit by a car?

773
01:00:53,850 --> 01:00:55,590
How could you know?

774
01:00:56,360 --> 01:00:59,150
There were only two people: myself and my husband.

775
01:01:01,450 --> 01:01:03,170
Three.

776
01:01:03,380 --> 01:01:05,510
I know this government would like us to think that

777
01:01:05,510 --> 01:01:06,910
they're savages,

778
01:01:06,910 --> 01:01:09,660
but Africans can speak as well as we can.

779
01:01:24,260 --> 01:01:25,300
Has it been busy?

780
01:01:25,750 --> 01:01:26,500
No.

781
01:01:27,770 --> 01:01:30,300
I came to see if Miriam would cook for the cafe.

782
01:01:32,370 --> 01:01:33,960
What did you say?

783
01:01:33,960 --> 01:01:38,540
I said that I have to mind the shop and the children.

784
01:01:39,690 --> 01:01:41,870
My wife doesn't need to work.

785
01:01:42,270 --> 01:01:44,300
Look,I'm sorry it's not a question of need...

786
01:01:44,300 --> 01:01:45,050
No!

787
01:01:48,300 --> 01:01:50,690
My wife doesn't know how to drive.

788
01:01:50,690 --> 01:01:53,030
I've told her time and again to take lessons,

789
01:01:53,030 --> 01:01:54,710
but she doesn't want to.

790
01:01:54,710 --> 01:01:56,250
If only she had...

791
01:01:56,250 --> 01:01:58,280
Oh,but I teach driving myself.

792
01:01:59,050 --> 01:02:02,740
Miriam,if you want me to come for a couple of hours a week,

793
01:02:03,210 --> 01:02:05,220
I'd be happy to come teach you.

794
01:02:05,520 --> 01:02:07,290
Thank you. Yes,I'd like that.

795
01:02:08,270 --> 01:02:11,930
My husband has been telling me I should learn

796
01:02:11,930 --> 01:02:14,430
how to drive for some time now.

797
01:02:15,370 --> 01:02:18,160
Good,then it's settled.

798
01:02:19,480 --> 01:02:21,360
I'll see you next week.

799
01:02:38,900 --> 01:02:40,240
Why did you do that?

800
01:02:40,240 --> 01:02:41,790
You know eggs are expensive.

801
01:02:41,790 --> 01:02:44,810
You have a long day in Cape Town.

802
01:02:46,670 --> 01:02:48,260
I may be staying the night.

803
01:03:03,050 --> 01:03:04,780
You're early...

804
01:03:07,750 --> 01:03:09,360
Very early.

805
01:03:09,970 --> 01:03:11,340
What happened?

806
01:03:12,480 --> 01:03:13,820
The market's closed.

807
01:03:13,820 --> 01:03:15,220
Closed?

808
01:03:15,220 --> 01:03:16,510
Why closed?

809
01:03:17,550 --> 01:03:19,420
Day of action by the blacks.

810
01:03:20,730 --> 01:03:22,140
Bloody blacks.

811
01:04:31,560 --> 01:04:34,570
Farah? Farah?

812
01:04:34,570 --> 01:04:37,650
Bhai, everything OK?

813
01:04:37,650 --> 01:04:38,700
My God!

814
01:04:38,700 --> 01:04:40,320
Bhai...

815
01:04:40,970 --> 01:04:43,370
Were you just going to surprise us like this?

816
01:04:43,370 --> 01:04:45,110
How good to see you!

817
01:04:45,110 --> 01:04:47,450
How did you know Sadru was back?

818
01:04:47,920 --> 01:04:50,300
I... I've finished early today...

819
01:04:50,600 --> 01:04:53,930
So I thought I'd stop in to say hello.

820
01:04:54,260 --> 01:04:55,770
I also finished early today...

821
01:04:55,770 --> 01:04:56,970
The demonstration...

822
01:05:00,330 --> 01:05:01,800
Family OK?

823
01:05:17,720 --> 01:05:18,930
Are you ready for me?

824
01:05:18,930 --> 01:05:21,210
Who else is going to teach me how to drive?

825
01:05:56,880 --> 01:05:59,660
OK,let's start with the pedals first.

826
01:06:00,110 --> 01:06:02,790
This is the gas pedal - the accelerator,

827
01:06:03,210 --> 01:06:04,930
and this is the... - Break.

828
01:06:05,220 --> 01:06:07,620
- Right,and this is the... - Clutch.

829
01:06:09,020 --> 01:06:10,370
Do you know how to drive?

830
01:06:10,370 --> 01:06:12,820
No. Why would I ask for lessons if I knew how to drive?

831
01:06:13,220 --> 01:06:14,200
I don't know.

832
01:06:14,200 --> 01:06:16,120
Maybe you wanted to see me.

833
01:06:20,310 --> 01:06:21,960
I don't know how to drive.

834
01:06:21,960 --> 01:06:25,280
But my husband showed me all the pedals

835
01:06:25,280 --> 01:06:28,160
once when he tried to teach me how to learn.

836
01:06:28,160 --> 01:06:31,890
There's only three, so it's not difficult.

837
01:06:33,450 --> 01:06:35,220
Do you know the gears too?

838
01:06:38,570 --> 01:06:39,320
No.

839
01:06:40,590 --> 01:06:41,810
I'll show you.

840
01:06:47,990 --> 01:06:49,000
Is madam inside?

841
01:06:49,000 --> 01:06:50,850
No,she's in the driving lesson,sir.

842
01:06:53,300 --> 01:06:55,830
There you are. See?

843
01:07:32,870 --> 01:07:34,000
Did he see us?

844
01:07:34,000 --> 01:07:35,340
No.

845
01:07:37,370 --> 01:07:39,060
We were having a driving lesson.

846
01:07:39,460 --> 01:07:41,080
I'm not finished yet.

847
01:07:42,710 --> 01:07:44,240
Get out of the truck.

848
01:07:47,950 --> 01:07:50,120
Miriam,we'll finish another time.

849
01:07:57,440 --> 01:07:58,820
How was your day?

850
01:07:58,820 --> 01:07:59,990
What?

851
01:07:59,990 --> 01:08:01,450
How was your day?

852
01:08:01,450 --> 01:08:02,570
Not good.

853
01:08:03,300 --> 01:08:04,410
Sorry to hear that.

854
01:08:04,410 --> 01:08:06,050
But things could get better.

855
01:08:20,560 --> 01:08:21,970
I want to talk to you.

856
01:08:23,860 --> 01:08:25,290
Where's Robert?

857
01:08:25,720 --> 01:08:27,080
Inside probably.

858
01:08:27,570 --> 01:08:29,510
I was angry with him earlier.

859
01:08:30,590 --> 01:08:33,090
Why are you angry with all of us?

860
01:08:33,710 --> 01:08:36,100
I should be angry with you.

861
01:08:40,050 --> 01:08:41,940
It's finished.

862
01:08:43,530 --> 01:08:45,520
I won't be seeing her anymore.

863
01:08:47,130 --> 01:08:49,090
Why did you do it,Omar?

864
01:08:51,930 --> 01:08:53,980
I don't know.

865
01:08:57,170 --> 01:08:58,590
There's mummy!

866
01:08:59,140 --> 01:09:00,660
I'll race you!

867
01:09:02,350 --> 01:09:03,960
You hurt me.

868
01:09:04,440 --> 01:09:06,130
Mummy,mummy!

869
01:09:08,030 --> 01:09:09,680
Come,come,come!

870
01:09:09,940 --> 01:09:11,030
Go,go,go,go,go!

871
01:09:18,160 --> 01:09:23,820
<i>"It won't be a stylish marriage, We can't afford a carriage..."</i>

872
01:09:24,640 --> 01:09:27,140
I've asked Madeline to have dinner with me.

873
01:09:28,510 --> 01:09:30,290
She accepted.

874
01:09:31,940 --> 01:09:33,480
Do you know what you're doing?

875
01:09:33,480 --> 01:09:34,890
I believe I do,yes.

876
01:09:34,890 --> 01:09:37,080
Where will you take her for dinner?

877
01:09:40,550 --> 01:09:43,550
I'm not fit to take her anywhere, am I?

878
01:09:43,790 --> 01:09:45,900
Only good enough to serve her a plate of food

879
01:09:45,900 --> 01:09:48,440
but not to sit and eat with her.

880
01:09:52,490 --> 01:09:54,120
You could bring her here.

881
01:09:56,760 --> 01:09:58,550
I'll think of something.

882
01:10:00,850 --> 01:10:06,160
I have lived my entire life in this place by their rules.

883
01:10:06,690 --> 01:10:10,290
I do not want to end my life alone because of them.

884
01:10:11,060 --> 01:10:12,440
I know.

885
01:10:13,250 --> 01:10:14,890
I know but

886
01:10:14,890 --> 01:10:18,080
lately I've been wondering whether it's worth

887
01:10:18,080 --> 01:10:20,630
going after certain people....

888
01:10:20,890 --> 01:10:23,260
...no matter how strongly you feel about them.

889
01:10:23,260 --> 01:10:25,030
You more than anyone

890
01:10:25,870 --> 01:10:28,850
has taught me that it is worth it.

891
01:10:29,850 --> 01:10:33,240
Don't start changing now,Amina.

892
01:10:51,260 --> 01:10:52,680
Hello.

893
01:10:54,210 --> 01:10:55,150
Hello,Robert.

894
01:10:55,150 --> 01:10:56,450
Miss.

895
01:10:56,450 --> 01:10:58,250
Are you ready?

896
01:11:11,610 --> 01:11:12,970
Robert?

897
01:11:13,880 --> 01:11:15,830
Take care of the shop please.

898
01:11:28,340 --> 01:11:31,270
You didn't come to give me a driving lesson,

899
01:11:32,940 --> 01:11:34,780
did you?

900
01:11:38,170 --> 01:11:40,040
Why did you come?

901
01:11:52,120 --> 01:11:54,050
I can't.

902
01:11:56,210 --> 01:11:58,190
I'm married.

903
01:11:59,610 --> 01:12:01,610
And you're a woman.

904
01:12:01,610 --> 01:12:03,530
Those are not good reasons.

905
01:12:05,490 --> 01:12:08,760
They are my reasons and they matter to me.

906
01:12:11,710 --> 01:12:13,680
Don't you care for me?

907
01:12:21,330 --> 01:12:23,450
Of course I care for you.

908
01:12:23,850 --> 01:12:25,330
Amina,please...

909
01:12:25,330 --> 01:12:27,270
Miriam.

910
01:12:28,770 --> 01:12:30,830
What am I doing to you?

911
01:12:33,800 --> 01:12:35,580
What am I doing to you?

912
01:12:37,900 --> 01:12:40,610
Every time I look at you

913
01:12:42,390 --> 01:12:44,860
I want you to stay...

914
01:12:46,230 --> 01:12:48,560
...forever.

915
01:13:05,590 --> 01:13:07,760
Will you do something for me?

916
01:13:09,500 --> 01:13:11,240
Close your eyes.

917
01:13:13,580 --> 01:13:15,520
You can trust me.

918
01:13:16,820 --> 01:13:18,610
I'm not afraid of you.

919
01:13:26,920 --> 01:13:28,660
Will you just imagine,

920
01:13:28,660 --> 01:13:30,800
just for now,

921
01:13:32,290 --> 01:13:35,640
just for brief moments,

922
01:13:36,960 --> 01:13:40,800
that nothing exists

923
01:13:41,070 --> 01:13:43,070
except for you and me?

924
01:14:11,820 --> 01:14:13,510
You need to go to her.

925
01:14:16,050 --> 01:14:16,800
No.

926
01:14:22,080 --> 01:14:23,850
What happens now?

927
01:14:27,330 --> 01:14:29,580
Do these driving lessons just continue?

928
01:14:36,940 --> 01:14:38,490
Come away with me!

929
01:14:39,200 --> 01:14:42,720
I have three children, who I'll never leave.

930
01:14:42,720 --> 01:14:45,370
I would never ask you to leave the children.

931
01:14:45,670 --> 01:14:47,200
We could...

932
01:14:47,580 --> 01:14:48,810
We could move.

933
01:14:48,810 --> 01:14:52,520
We could move away from him,Miriam, and I will look after you and the children.

934
01:14:53,010 --> 01:14:56,770
Amina,please...

935
01:14:56,770 --> 01:14:58,360
Miriam,I know...

936
01:14:58,360 --> 01:15:00,950
I know that you think I don't know what I'm talking about,

937
01:15:01,260 --> 01:15:04,740
but I've lived this way,Miriam, I've lived my own way my whole life,

938
01:15:04,740 --> 01:15:06,010
and it can be done!

939
01:15:06,010 --> 01:15:07,250
- Amina! - It can be done,Miriam.

940
01:15:07,510 --> 01:15:08,470
Amina...

941
01:15:10,900 --> 01:15:14,130
Not for me.

942
01:16:24,260 --> 01:16:25,670
Ah,Jacob!

943
01:16:26,530 --> 01:16:27,840
Do you need a hand?

944
01:16:27,840 --> 01:16:29,970
If you wouldn't mind. I'm struggling with this lock.

945
01:16:29,970 --> 01:16:31,580
Here,let me do it.

946
01:16:35,410 --> 01:16:36,690
Hello.

947
01:16:37,450 --> 01:16:38,750
Hello?

948
01:16:38,750 --> 01:16:40,110
Police here,ma'am.

949
01:16:40,110 --> 01:16:41,840
Post-mistress here,sir.

950
01:16:42,270 --> 01:16:43,490
Are you alright?

951
01:16:43,490 --> 01:16:45,860
I was driving by and I saw the door ajar.

952
01:16:45,860 --> 01:16:48,290
Oh,I'm fine,thank you. Just locking up.

953
01:16:48,670 --> 01:16:49,690
Sorry to trouble you.

954
01:16:49,910 --> 01:16:51,320
No trouble.

955
01:16:55,350 --> 01:16:56,850
Who's there?

956
01:16:59,770 --> 01:17:00,650
This is Jacob.

957
01:17:00,650 --> 01:17:02,920
The section where you are standing is for whites only.

958
01:17:02,920 --> 01:17:04,670
He was just helping me lock up.

959
01:17:04,670 --> 01:17:05,900
He shouldn't be there.

960
01:17:05,900 --> 01:17:07,570
Who is he anyway?

961
01:17:08,330 --> 01:17:10,330
He's my driver.

962
01:17:19,090 --> 01:17:21,270
Why doesn't your driver keep the keys?

963
01:17:21,270 --> 01:17:23,200
Coz I prefer to keep them myself.

964
01:17:23,200 --> 01:17:24,580
Yeah,I know what you mean...

965
01:17:24,980 --> 01:17:26,550
Better to be safe than sorry.

966
01:17:26,550 --> 01:17:28,090
Quite...

967
01:17:56,780 --> 01:17:59,570
I thought I told you not to disturb me?!!

968
01:18:01,290 --> 01:18:03,480
Yes,but that was when you were six years old,no?

969
01:18:06,950 --> 01:18:08,270
Dad...

970
01:18:09,240 --> 01:18:11,250
I'm sorry, I thought that...

971
01:18:11,910 --> 01:18:15,780
You come! I thought that you were Doris or one of the girls.

972
01:18:17,430 --> 01:18:18,700
Just me.

973
01:18:25,610 --> 01:18:27,720
Can I get you something to eat?

974
01:18:27,720 --> 01:18:28,940
Some tea?

975
01:18:28,940 --> 01:18:31,020
No,no,I'm fine.

976
01:18:32,670 --> 01:18:36,470
No,we just... we haven't heard from you for 3 weeks and your...

977
01:18:37,550 --> 01:18:39,970
so your mother's worried and I just came to check...

978
01:18:39,970 --> 01:18:41,880
to see you're OK.

979
01:18:44,540 --> 01:18:45,930
I'm fine.

980
01:18:46,520 --> 01:18:47,600
Good.

981
01:18:51,390 --> 01:18:53,050
Things have been... um...

982
01:18:55,990 --> 01:18:57,050
It's hard to explain.

983
01:18:57,050 --> 01:18:58,430
No need.

984
01:19:00,380 --> 01:19:02,530
You see,people like to make sure your mother and I

985
01:19:02,530 --> 01:19:05,370
know everything that is happening with you.

986
01:19:06,770 --> 01:19:09,070
They wouldn't like us to miss out.

987
01:19:11,590 --> 01:19:13,860
Only this time people are...

988
01:19:15,130 --> 01:19:18,400
Amina,people are talking about her,not just you.

989
01:19:19,860 --> 01:19:21,230
They know her as well.

990
01:19:21,230 --> 01:19:22,860
They have no right.

991
01:19:23,120 --> 01:19:26,270
It's only because she's friends with me that they make any assumptions.

992
01:19:27,800 --> 01:19:29,810
Don't people have anything better to do?!

993
01:19:30,040 --> 01:19:31,680
No,they don't.

994
01:19:33,440 --> 01:19:35,220
That's why I try to avoid them.

995
01:20:02,170 --> 01:20:03,870
Jacob,

996
01:20:03,870 --> 01:20:06,500
I'm so terribly sorry about what happened.

997
01:20:07,960 --> 01:20:10,250
I'm ashamed to say that I was afraid of that young policeman,

998
01:20:10,250 --> 01:20:13,190
and what he might do to you if he suspected...

999
01:20:13,190 --> 01:20:14,880
It's alright.

1000
01:20:15,460 --> 01:20:17,930
Probably they'd thrown me in jail if they'd guessed.

1001
01:20:17,930 --> 01:20:20,190
Jacob,come inside.

1002
01:20:20,390 --> 01:20:22,090
I'll make us some supper.

1003
01:20:23,670 --> 01:20:25,100
I can't.

1004
01:20:27,850 --> 01:20:30,840
I hope you understand.

1005
01:20:32,770 --> 01:20:35,180
Yes,I understand.

1006
01:20:36,930 --> 01:20:38,390
I am sorry.

1007
01:20:41,740 --> 01:20:44,270
- I-I-I want to drive you home. - No.

1008
01:20:48,900 --> 01:20:50,760
Goodbye,Madeline.

1009
01:20:56,840 --> 01:20:58,680
Goodbye,Jacob.

1010
01:20:59,860 --> 01:21:01,800
Goodbye.

1011
01:21:21,030 --> 01:21:22,460
So,you're running away?

1012
01:21:22,460 --> 01:21:26,050
No,I just need some time,I just need some time away to think,dad.

1013
01:21:32,370 --> 01:21:33,570
Do you need money?

1014
01:21:33,570 --> 01:21:34,320
No.

1015
01:21:35,680 --> 01:21:37,410
Thank you.

1016
01:21:41,960 --> 01:21:43,630
You shouldn't go.

1017
01:21:47,320 --> 01:21:49,780
How will she know where to find you?!

1018
01:22:02,590 --> 01:22:04,230
What a day!

1019
01:22:08,570 --> 01:22:10,840
Did you have your driving lesson today?

1020
01:22:10,840 --> 01:22:11,590
No.

1021
01:22:13,820 --> 01:22:15,200
Good.

1022
01:22:16,190 --> 01:22:17,440
That's over then.

1023
01:22:17,440 --> 01:22:18,190
No.

1024
01:22:19,460 --> 01:22:22,890
I have to learn how to drive if I'm going to work.

1025
01:22:23,370 --> 01:22:25,130
You work here.

1026
01:22:26,620 --> 01:22:29,210
And I will still work here.

1027
01:22:29,630 --> 01:22:33,130
And I will work at the cafe for two mornings a week.

1028
01:22:35,770 --> 01:22:37,430
You don't need to work.

1029
01:22:38,310 --> 01:22:39,850
I do.

1030
01:22:40,070 --> 01:22:43,130
It's just for two mornings, just let me learn how to drive.

1031
01:22:43,130 --> 01:22:45,840
You will not be my wife and work!

1032
01:22:46,790 --> 01:22:48,890
Do you wanna divorce me?

1033
01:22:48,890 --> 01:22:50,890
What about the children?

1034
01:22:52,060 --> 01:22:53,620
What is it,Omar?

1035
01:22:54,170 --> 01:22:56,140
Tell me what you're thinking.

1036
01:23:03,180 --> 01:23:04,590
Mummy!

1037
01:23:07,770 --> 01:23:09,010
It's OK.

1038
01:23:09,860 --> 01:23:13,760
It's alright,my love. Everything's OK. Go back to sleep.

1039
01:23:15,140 --> 01:23:16,530
It's alright.

1040
01:23:32,560 --> 01:23:34,850
I don't like it.

1041
01:23:35,950 --> 01:23:39,600
If I don't like it, that should be enough.

1042
01:23:41,400 --> 01:23:43,440
It's not enough.

1043
01:23:44,680 --> 01:23:46,910
It never has been.

1044
01:23:48,260 --> 01:23:51,410
I just didn't know what to tell you until now.

1045
01:23:55,420 --> 01:23:56,170
No!

1046
01:23:56,850 --> 01:23:59,480
You'll have to find a better way of speaking to me.

1047
01:24:11,140 --> 01:24:13,090
Not again!

1048
01:24:33,590 --> 01:24:36,480
I may still need some lessons.

1049
01:24:39,570 --> 01:24:41,890
You drove all the way from Delhof?!

1050
01:24:42,130 --> 01:24:44,400
Do you still have that vacancy?

1051
01:24:47,460 --> 01:24:49,260
Two days a week?

1052
01:24:59,250 --> 01:25:03,350
If it works out, even more...

1053
01:25:14,640 --> 01:25:16,090
Come on then.

1054
01:25:19,660 --> 01:25:21,380
I'm Miriam.

1055
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


1056
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


