They don't understand my accent.
Did you try?
I'll call tomorrow.
This isn't even American.
How are you going to learn English?
"Longing...
longing for a wave of love
to swell up in me."
Like a lady.
Ba, did we wake you?
School project.
Paul made a braised pork sausage.
Pretty tasty.
Yours is in the microwave.
When Ellie's Ma died...
I fell into a dark hole.
I didn't move for days.
A few days later...
I woke to find Ellie in the booth...
manning the switch.
She looked up at me.
Just 13... an adult already.
And I...
smiled.
This is a lot of dumplings.
Six days, 18 meals.
To Grinnell.
We didn't come here
so you could be like me.
We came here
so you could be like your mother.
God, I hope not.